You are a crypto [music] investor, you
have to watch this video.
This new token launched less than a week
ago and has absolutely [music] taken
over the crypto space.
>> [music]
[music]
>> What is up, everybody? Welcome back to
the master class with Jake and Rodney.
Rodney, it's fun shirt Friday once
again. I got my fun shirt on. You got
your fun shirt on and we have a hell of
a show planned tonight, Rodney. One of
the most influential men in the crypto
space for cycles now, not just one
cycle. The guy's done it for many
cycles. Crashis Clay, some call him the
goat, some call him the Warren Buffett
of meme coins. He's going to be joining
us here in about 15 minutes on this
spectacular Friday, Rodney. How you
doing, first off?
>> I mean, you you can't feel bad on a fun
shirt Friday. We got a good story about
Jake about his fun shirt before this. Um
but, you know, super pumped to have, you
could say the goat of meme coin callers,
um in the space. A person that's been
kind of hiding away during the pump fun
meme coin uh craze. So, it's good to
have him back with the holding culture
and I'm feeling good, man. I'm ready to,
you know, talk about some meme coins and
hang out with the boys.
>> Absolutely. It's Friday, guys. And look,
if you are here right now, I've been
saying this for a while, I've been
tweeting it for a while, you do not make
money at the peak of the bull runs,
right? At the top of the markets when
everyone comes in in 2021, at the peak
of the bull run in 2025, you make money
now when not many people are in crypto,
uh when everybody the the retail
investors are not here, and when the big
communities are forming and we've seen
Crash tweet about some good tokens here,
Rodney,
in the past couple of weeks on X. I'm
excited just to hear his his thoughts,
you know, he had some great calls,
really, really good calls last cycle. I
mean, Brett, I'm pretty sure he kind of
had his claim to fame, if you will. He
put $15,000 into Brett on Base, turned
it into many, many millions. I mean,
Brett went to a over a $2.5 billion
market cap with zero support from
Coinbase and Base, I should add, and
we're going to talk about to Crash about
that as well. But now is the time to
lock in, now is the time to pay
attention. And Rodney, if you look at
what happened with tokens back in 2022,
2023, tokens like SPX, like Pepe, like
Mog, like WIF, like Bonk, most of these
tokens, I mean, look at SPX, it's a
great example, it traded below a $10
million market cap for a year, a year, a
community formed, and then it was
trading above a $2.5 billion market cap
as well. So now is the time to lock in.
If you are watching this at home, ladies
and gentlemen, make sure to retweet
this. We're live on Kick, shout out to
everybody on Kick, we're live on my X,
and we're also live on Crash Us Clay's
YouTube channel, so go over there, hit
that subscribe button, and let's make it
happen. But Rodney, first off, you know,
we have to start off this show every
single time with a quick look at the
markets. Let's see what's taking place
in the crypto space today. So
>> Not a lot of good.
>> Not a lot of good, but not a lot of bad.
Bitcoin is at $75,000
right now, Ethereum at $2,071,
BNB at 652, XRP at $1.33.
Solana still at 85 bucks.
Dogecoin at 10 cents. Hyperliquid just
hit a new all-time high above $55.
>> Sheesh.
>> Up 23% on the week. Zcash $600, Cardano
doing nothing, 24 cents. I mean, I
thought if you, you know, if you're
going to sell Cardano, I thought most
people would just have sold by now at 24
cents. Monero at 381.
Toncoin has slipped under $2 after it
ripped. Toncoin really ripped in the
past past month after Pavel Durov
announced that Telegram was going to be
one of the main validators for the TON
blockchain. Sweet.
Sweet? Sweet going to go below a dollar?
At a dollar and six and Avalanche $9.22.
We'll finish with our favorite token,
one of our favorite tokens, Ronnie,
which is Pepe. Well, first we got to
talk about Astra, 67 cents, still
looking good. And Pepe at a $1.5 billion
market cap. So,
that is the crypto markets today,
Ronnie. What are your thoughts? Not
really looking too good, but I mean,
we're in the middle of a bear market.
It's not supposed to look good right
now.
>> Yeah, blood red day. A day when the
stock market hit an all-time high again.
Shout out to AI, but yeah, blood red
day. But like you said before, you know,
with meme coins you can hold for large
projects you can hold for an extended
amount of like extended amount of time.
This is the time where you're supposed
to get in, where the hype is gone,
right? Coinbase volume is down,
everybody's creating fud articles, all
the retail is gone. This is This is the
sweet spot where you find like those
good plays where everybody like All the
meme coin guys who are making meme coin
videos are all talking about uh uh the
SpaceX IPO and are sponsored by
Polymarket, which we're not opposed to
being sponsored by What I'm saying is
everybody left the space, so the people
that are here grinding and looking for
those top plays
are the ones that are going to win. You
don't win when you get in when everybody
else gets in.
>> No, and I think look, I'm excited for
the show because I've won big on a lot
of crashes calls. And I've like publicly
supported him. People are like, "Oh,
stop sucking his Yeah, I'm like, dude,
the guy has made great calls and I've
made a lot of money. Like, he's one of
the most consistent to do it and and
like I don't know why. I don't know how
old he is. I don't know where he's from,
but he just understands meme coins
better than most people. Like and it's
just a skill and it's really cuz he
spent 10,000 hours in the meme coin
space and understands it, right? But he
just he has a good feel for it. So, I I
I really do believe it. It's May 22nd,
2026. I think that the knowledge that's
dropped in this show could potentially
make a lot of people a lot of money,
right? And that's just being honest
because of where we're at in this
particular market. But Rodney,
we just talked about the markets. Some
big news
a [laughter] hack
>> Yes.
>> your in the crypto space. Tell me about
what happened with Polymarket. I
actually haven't seen it. $600,000 hack?
What exactly happened? An exploit on
Polymarket?
>> Yes, so we had a big exploit. First of
all, you know, Polymarket um let me go
ahead and just if you want to share my
screen.
>> Yep, got you.
>> Okay.
>> You got to bring it up. I don't see it
here.
>> Uh should be up.
There it is.
Boom.
There it is. Boom. I got it right there.
Okay, so you know, obviously Polymarket,
big daddy when it comes to prediction
markets. I mean, this is like the
hottest thing right now. It say out of
anything I you know, in the financial
world world you can say. I mean, you can
bet on anything. Jake, I make a I made a
joke that you can probably uh make a bet
on how many you know, shits the
president's going to take. Like insane
bets.
>> Trump he's probably taking like, I don't
know. He just drinks diet coke and I
mean, with diet coke and McDonald's he's
probably taking two or three a day.
>> Oh dude, healthy but healthy guy though,
you know, Donald Trump for for a guy who
eats McDonald's and drinks coke all he's
healthy. And he has way more energy than
I do. But yeah, there was a a big
exploit this morning. There was a lot of
confusion. A lot of people were saying
it was a hack. Like the main kind of
platform got hacked, but that was not
the case. Um so this was the alert this
morning and then we got some news from
DGN News says Polymarket VP of DeFi
engineering, uh his name is Josh Steven
says they are investigating transactions
flagged as suspicious as suspicious,
excuse me. Zack XBT and others says it's
not a contract hack. This looks like a
very old PK which has been compromised.
So privacy keys, right? So
So check this out. So this is from Josh.
Uh looks like yeah, this is the guy we
were just talking about the main VP of
um
kind of like marketing and stuff like
that. No Polymarket or UMA contracts
have been exploited. All user funds are
safe and using poly uh market.com is
safe. Uh so business as usual. So we had
a 6-year-old private key that was
compromised. This was in the internal
top-up config, which is why funds were
being sent to it. So pretty much
$600,000 of just polygon. It said poly,
so I thought it was like the token, but
it's actually matic, but they changed
matic to poly
was stolen. The exploit stopped. And
pretty much just someone got some
private keys and you know a pretty an
exploit. So you know, crime is rampant
in crypto still. Poly market is safe as
a platform, but you know, on a day like
this where there's nothing to really
talk about except for we you know, we
have crash coming on the show. It's nice
to have something going on, right?
>> Yeah, 6-year-old private key that was
compromised. Very interesting stuff
here. And I guess that's just a a good
time to talk about security for your
assets, right? For anyone that's
watching. We already have 1,100 people
who are here on X, guys. A lot more on
Crash's YouTube. The number one thing
that is going to get you wrecked is if
you get packed, you click a link,
someone steals your money. And trust me,
the fishing scams out there are insane.
All you have to do now, I see it right
now on my Twitter account, the the fake
Jake Gagan accounts are coming back
saying, "Hey, we're launching this
giveaway. Click this link." If you click
the link and you just have your assets
in a Phantom wallet or a a MetaMask,
you're at risk of losing it, right? So
the number one thing you can do, get a
hardware wallet. That's the the best way
to keep your assets safe. And then
always just verify. I mean, there's so
many scammers out there. The amount of
people are like, "Jake, is this you
messaging me on TikTok or Telegram?" I'm
like, "No, that's not me. So you need to
be careful."
>> and everything. Yeah.
>> Yeah, exactly. It's like, "Hello, how
you trade go?" I'm like, "Does that
sound like me?" Like, "No, it's that's
not me."
>> And the thing is with some of these,
it's usually just like typical day one
like fishing scams. Like local singles
in your area, some like spoofed email or
something like that. And you know, I've
had friends who are not even in the
crypto, but they get emails from
Coinbase. Like that's how crazy it is.
Emails from MetaMask, which MetaMask
doesn't email you. So just crazy [__]
you see online, you know.
>> It works. Just be careful, guys. You
have to you really like it's tough, you
know, if you have your money in stocks
on Schwab, it's pretty safe. You have
your money in Chase Bank, it's pretty
safe. If you have a million dollars or a
hundred million dollars on a hardware
wallet or even an exchange or in a
MetaMask, like dude, that money is not
safe. One click and we need to do
something like we have AI now. Why don't
we have something that can like why
can't Grok create a way to warn you when
there's a malicious link, right? Like
hey, like just a red arrow. I might I
might have my Grok. I might trade my
Claude code AI bots on that. Like hey,
let's create something that can identify
if there's a malicious link that's going
to steal all your crypto instead of just
having these scam links run rampant, but
it's crazy, man. All the SIM swapping
that was happening, all the accounts
that were getting hacked on Twitter
launching the rug pulls. Crypto is the
wild, wild west and unfortunately, it's
still is the wild, wild west.
>> Yeah, it's like a you know, if you if
you have a bank or something like that
or maybe you send like the wrong Venmo
transaction, you can call the people up
and get that transaction reversed. If
you accidentally send some funds from a
wallet to another wallet, you got to
hope that the person sends it back. And
if it's some sort of fishing scam,
you're you're just [__] out of luck,
right? It And luckily, typical regular
anti-viruses will give you like a little
green or red check on links if you have
it enabled. So, there's that too.
>> Yeah, yeah, yeah.
>> even have that.
>> Mhm.
>> I like it. I like it. Uh let's say
what's up to the comments real quick. Uh
we got House, baby. A lot of people in
here, guys. A lot of people are here.
Shout out to everybody. Hackers of a
hack. We got X. We got Cash Out. We got
The Vocals. We got Zack Zolfam. We got a
lot of people here.
In here, guys. A lot of crash reporters
are in here. Shout out to KB9. We see
you. Uh and we have @ The Vocal says we
love crash. Guys, we're going to be
bringing on Cat Crash in about 5
minutes. If you haven't yet, make sure
to retweet this space on X, guys. Drop
some comments and we're going to be
having a good show here in just a bit.
Now, Rodney, we have to talk about
another piece of news. I'm going to go
ahead and pull up my screen here. And
we've been talking about this token
quite a bit on this show. We've been
talking about the Tom blockchain, why
we're bullish on it. Now, I don't know
if you saw this, Rodney.
>> Oh, I did.
>> Go ahead and share this. One
>> Oh.
>> [laughter]
>> One second. Glitch Glitch the Matrix.
Oh.
>> Hold on. I have it here if you want it.
>> Yeah, go ahead and pull up yours.
>> Boom. This You You reposted this.
>> I did repost this, yes. So,
click this Go ahead and zoom in. Click
this video. And this is Pavel Durov. For
So, for those that don't know, guys,
Pavel Durov And shout out to Mike Farley
in the chat. We got Mike Farley here.
>> What's up, Mike?
>> What's up, my guy? So, Pavel Durov is
the founder of Telegram, right? And for
those that don't know, guys, recently
recently very recently, I think it was
like 2 weeks ago, uh Pavel Durov made a
post saying, "Hey, the TON token, which
is the Open Network token, which is it
wasn't backed by Telegram right away
because Joe Biden and Gary Gensler
wouldn't allow Telegram to have a
cryptocurrency project, right, back in
the day. But now that regulations kind
of be become a little bit looser under
the Trump administration,
>> A lot of it was under the
>> 2 weeks 2 weeks ago,
that
Telegram is going to be the main
validator for the Open Network. That
sent the price of Telegram from about a
dollar to $2.50. And now, Rodney, go
ahead and play this video. It's a
9-second video from Pavel Durov. And you
can see
>> I got it right here, yeah. Who do we see
there? Uh a little special yellow duck,
right?
>> You can see the yellow duck. So, play
the full video. So, he's saying that,
you know, AI agents are now going to be
able to take over your inbox, etc. And
right here, you'll see that he is soft
shaming
the Uchiya duck. He's soft shaming the
Uchiya duck.
>> The tokens or the
>> Which are you talking about? Go ahead.
>> So, what came first, the token or the
duck?
>> Uh
I think the duck, yeah. So, the Uchiya
duck, guys, and shout out to Sarah. She
just reposted the stream. The Uchiya
duck is literally integrated within
Telegram. And I've been seeing the duck
for about 3 or 4 years now. Whenever,
you know, I upload large files, large
video files, send them to our editors,
whenever you do that, it takes a certain
amount of time to send it. And the
Uchiya duck is like a little icon that
they use when you're sending videos. So,
the Utya duck, in my opinion, is the
mascot of Telegram, and the fact that
Pavel Durov is soft shilling the Utya
duck, which to me, that's what I took it
as, right? He's soft shilling the Utya
duck here on May 21st, 2026, guys. It
just It leads me to believe that this is
going to be a billion-dollar runner on
the TON blockchain. Let me see if Look,
I think my camera's a little bit messed
up. Let me just test this out real
quick. Share screen.
>> Yeah, I don't know why it wasn't
working.
>> Let me see if it's working here. Not my
camera. But, okay, we're working now.
So,
>> It's mine.
>> Let's see if mine's working. 3 2 1.
Glitch? Nope. All right, we're back.
Cool. So, this is the Utya duck, guys.
Pavel Durov, literally, how many
followers does this guy have? 2.9
million followers, following one,
absolute chad. His His interview with
Lex Fridman, I was like I sent all my
friends, I'm like, "If you are a [__]
man, you need to listen to this 4-hour
long interview." I listened to it. I was
like, "Fuck it, I got to go for a run."
I ran like 6 miles, came back home, I'm
working out. He's an absolute giga chad,
guys. I mean, you look at the founders
in cryptocurrency, you got Charles
Hoskinson, you got the guys from Solana,
you got Vitalik Buterin. Look, all very,
very smart, and they're all right, but
not necessarily [__] studs. Pavel
Durov, this guy hasn't had a piece of
sugar in his life, never had alcohol,
never touched a drug, doesn't doesn't
drink at all, sleeps like, I think 12 or
15 hours a day.
>> Like He is He works out. He ice baths
every day, saunas every day. He said
when he wakes up, he does 100 push-ups
or 300 push-ups, 300 squats, hops in ice
bath. Like, he is the definition of a
[__] absolute giga chad. And now, he
is, in my opinion, trying to be a main
character in the crypto space this
cycle. He got to Bitcoin like 2009,
started one of the most profitable and
best social media sites in Russia. They
were spying on him. He moved to Dubai,
started the number one messaging app in
the world, which is Telegram. And now,
he's bull posting about TON, he's bull
posting about Telegram, and he's soft
shilling Utya, Ronnie, which is a
bullish sign. Now, we've shown the Uta
charts multiple time right around a $30
million market cap today. And this is
one of those tokens that I talked about.
I talked about SPX and Mog, you know,
and and and with trading underneath a
$10 million market cap for a long time.
Uta,
I mean, almost what is this? This is
from April 2024
>> Okay.
>> until August of 2025, 13, 14 months, 15
months it traded below a $10 million
market cap, had some, you know, a little
bit of run up in August, and it ran to a
$60 million market cap here, guys.
Finding a nice floor above a $30 million
market cap. But, if I was a betting man,
which I am a betting man,
I'm going to bet that Uta is going to be
the first billion-dollar meme coin on
Ton. Pavel Durov is soft shilling it
here during a bear market. What do you
think happens when Ton starts to rip?
More people come into the Ton ecosystem.
We're going to see tokens like Uta and
other meme coins on Ton absolutely fly.
So, I'm looking forward to it, Ronnie.
Shout out to Pavel Durov, giga chad.
Look, there are some
There are some banners there.
>> [laughter]
>> I got like 10 things
>> is going on in the 10 things going on in
the background.
>> But, it's okay.
>> It's okay. But, anyway, shout out to
shout out to
Uta. And shout out to Shera. Shera's
been bull posting Uta for quite some
time at a $30 million market cap. Now,
Ronnie, I see that our special guest
just joined us, guys. Drop some
comments, guys. I want to see the
comments flooded with the word crash. I
want to see the comments flooded with
the word crash.
>> Yeah, we need to get some crashes
>> In the comments, act like we're like
Imagine we were in the live a studio at
a auditorium. I want everyone chanting
crash in the comments. Drop some crashes
in the comments. Let's get him in.
Crash, crash, crash, crash. I'm not
bringing him in till the whole audience
is saying crash. There we go. The whole
audience is saying crash.
>> I'm helping.
>> Crash, crash, crash, crash. Let's get
him in, ladies and gentlemen. A warm
welcome to the Warren Buffett of meme
coins,
Crashes Clay. Crash, how we doing, my
brother?
>> What's up, baby?
>> I'm good, happy to be alive, not even
kidding. I got to start off by saying I
went into nonexistence today or like I
felt like I died, bro.
Not even kidding cuz
I I was getting blood work today for the
first time cuz I'm trying to check my T
levels.
And I've fainted multiple times growing
up getting like, you know, a needle, the
shots, and [__] And today, bro, I would
like first 30 seconds they're drawing my
blood. I'm like, "That's chill. This is
easy. Everything's going good. This
doesn't hurt." And then bam, I just
faint and um next thing I wake up, my
whole body is just drenched in sweat.
I'm super hot. And bro, oh my gosh, it
it was just
That felt horrible. I wake up, bro, and
I was just so happy to be alive, bro. Oh
my gosh, it's good to be here.
>> Squeamish.
We're happy to have you here. You know
what's funny, bro, is that used to
happen to me cuz my mom has like white
coat syndrome. And then I got a bunch of
like I like the first time I ever got my
blood drawn, I fainted, right? I I was
like 4/16 playing baseball, you got to
get it done. Uh but I recently, you
know, it's funny, dude, we would be best
friends if we like knew each other in
person. I think we're best friends
online, but we'd be best friends IRL,
Crash, cuz I recently got my blood uh
drawn 2 weeks ago just to get my
testosterone tested, my blood work,
STDs, by the way, clean as a whistle
STDs. My testosterone level, Crash,
ready for this? All natural, ready for
this?
>> 1,100, bro.
>> Yeah, did I send it to you?
>> No, you didn't. I just guessed.
>> bro? I'm 1,150.
Nuts. Horny.
I Yeah, all natural. How'd you know
that? I didn't even send that to you.
I'm literally 1,150.
>> I I
I promise I just guessed, dude. That's
crazy.
>> You can feel it. But for those that are
at home
Yeah, for those that are at for those
that are at home, an average like like
on the the reader, like the doctor will
send you like what's the average range.
It's like 250 to 750. I'm 1,150, all
natural. Just 30 years old, fighting
Jewish muscle. I run a lot. I work out a
lot. We like to have a little bit of
cardio after No, I'm just kidding. But
yeah, just just exercise, eating good
food, working out, sunshine.
And uh uh I think that's the secret to
high T. But you're all about high T.
>> Yeah, I mean that's why I'm excited to
see cuz I've actually never tested in my
life for that. So, you know, it's going
to be funny when it comes back to like
600, 700, bro. And I'm just going to be
like regular as [__] but I'm waiting
and I'm excited to see the results. So.
>> It's probably high. And honestly, you
can work on it. And yeah, I mean I'm all
natural. I know a lot of people like,
"Dude, like clavicular, right?" He's
like 19 years old doing TRT since 16.
It's like peptides and [__] It's like,
"Bro, you don't even need that." You
just need to work out, be healthy, have
fun, get a lot of sunshine, eat good
food, and it will naturally go up.
>> I think it A lot of the guys are just
trying to take some shortcuts. You know
what I mean? Whatever is hot right now,
you know, they're going to take it.
>> There are no shortcuts in life, man.
Like you you got to put the work in
regardless. Like I know I mean, look at
all the people that are on Ozempic right
now. Like yeah, that is a shortcut. But
like look at their faces, bro. They're
all [__]
sucked out. Like it's not healthy. Like
sure, you might take a pill. And there's
also studies coming out right now that
when you take Ozempic, it kind of
uh
curbs your appetite for food, but it's
also curbing your appetite for
everything else. Like these people are
finding it harder to stay in love, to
find hobbies, like to enjoy life because
you're shutting off something in your
brain that's not wanting food. It's also
not wanting other things in your life,
as well. So. I I don't know. Crash, what
are your thoughts on that? Are there any
shortcuts in life? I mean, if there are,
I'm still trying to find one.
>> I mean,
I think one of the biggest shortcuts are
meme coins, even though people are going
to [__] on them always, you know. But
that's that's legit one of the shortcuts
in life, you know. But honestly, there's
not that many.
That's why I'm in memes, bro. It's
[__] You know, they say smart people
always try to find the easiest way to
win, right? So.
Yeah.
>> Even crypto, though.
>> Yeah.
>> Even crypto, some people would consider
a shortcut, right? Like I mean, buying
Bitcoin, it went from 15K to 126,000
last cycle. Solana went from $8 to 290.
What exactly about meme coins? I mean,
you let's let's just talk about cuz some
people might be new here, you know, to
this channel and and to you. Kind of
give them like your background in terms
of
your your meme coin run cuz you had one
of the
I would say Murad had a great uh
purchase with SPX and held very long.
You purchased $15,000 worth of Brett on
a public wallet when it first launched
after a couple days or a couple hours,
whenever it was. And then it ran to What
was the all-time high in that You turned
$15,000 into how much with one purchase
of a meme coin?
>> At the peak was 15 million and
that's literally 1,000x on the entry. It
hit 2.3 billion.
And yeah, still hold it there, so.
>> Holy [__] You turned Let's repeat that.
You turned $15,000
into $15 million
with one purchase on a meme coin and
that token was Brett on Base. That's
insane. That's like you can't do that
anywhere else and you're really one of
the only people that did that last cycle
in crypto.
>> Yeah, I mean, also wasn't just Brett on
Bobo, 30,000 into around 2.1 million. On
Resistance Dog was around 35,000 into
around 1.5 to 2 million. So, it wasn't
just like it was only on one play, you
know, on Ponkeo it was up over a
million. So, that's a thing and
I don't I don't know. Where else can you
put Yeah, I get it. It's not like I was
putting one grand into it, you know.
Yeah, sure I was putting 15 to 30 grand,
but still, okay, if you scale that down
and you're only putting one grand,
you're turning one grand on Brett,
that's a a mil one grand into a million,
literally.
You know?
>> That's insane. Yeah, I mean, that's a
return. Not bad.
>> So,
even even if you don't make a 1,000x or
500x or 200x, bro, still 30x, 50x, 100x
is good. Uh it's insane, you know? It's
It's not that many asymmetric
opportunities for a regular guy to do
that. And I know I'm a regular [__]
guy, you know? Like, yeah, I think about
things probably a little more deeply
than others. I, you know, I think about
these things more, but still,
uh, trust me. I
I have to
depend on others for little things that
even I'll be like, damn, why, you know,
like, I don't know. This is just an
example. A carpenter, he has to make
some furniture, some wood. And I feel
bad. I feel like, man, why can't I build
stuff? Why can't I do this stuff, you
know? Or like, connecting some lights
or, you know, fixing a toilet. I can't
do any of that [__] So, I feel very
deficient in things like that. So, you
know, but guess what? You can be
deficient in other areas and still be
pretty damn good at memes because yeah,
I always tell people
>> Yeah? No, I was just going to say, and
sorry to cut you off, but I mean, but
can you pay for someone to do that?
Like, I just have I just moved into a
new apartment. And
bro, I bro, I can't put up I mean, I
could put up a TV, but like, bro, the
guys, like, and shout-out to my guy
Danny and Charlie, they came over and
set up my whole apartment. And dude,
they did every They They took the
couches, the beds, the mattress, they
hung [__] up, they did everything. And I
probably could do it, but I just paid
them. They're my friends, keep the money
in the family. And you Like, I work
hard, we stream, we we invest in crypto
so you can afford those lifestyles. So,
you're not always going to be great at
everything, but I'm sure you're great at
stuff, right? You do jujitsu, uh, Muay
Thai, you built an online brand, you
help a lot of people make money. So, the
carpenter, he wishes that he could He
envies you for doing that, right?
Whereas you're like, oh, I'm a deficient
in these areas, but you're never going
to be good at everything. So, you just
got to find the things that you want to
be good at and and get good at those.
Yeah, I mean,
I agree.
>> I mean, you don't got you
I think Ronnie's cut out.
>> mean, Ronnie's cut out.
>> of things, bro. Ronnie, you built in the
matrix, doggy.
>> Made a bunch of money, made I've lost a
lot of people money as well, you could
say, right? Cuz if made anyone money,
that means I've also lost people money,
cuz you can't give me credit for making
anyone money.
Uh you know, without giving me the
discredit of also people can lose money.
But that's why I don't believe I make
anyone money, and I don't believe I lose
anyone money.
>> Yeah.
>> I just believe Look, I buy things before
they go up a lot. Some people are able
to buy things before they go up a lot,
and some people are
commonly late. Some people only buy in a
green candle. Some people only buy when
things are pumping up 100x, you know? Of
course, those people are always going to
lose, you know?
But uh that's why it's important now,
whenever it's the bear market, whenever
Bitcoin is dropping, whenever attention
on tweets, on live streams is low,
right? The viewership we're going to
have today is going to be 10 times lower
than in a bull run. Right? So, this is
the time where legitimately the 10% can
win, because well, only the 10% are left
here, you know? And then in the future,
the 90% come back as they always do.
They rush into the green, and they
excitement. That's the thing. That's why
I'm I'm here now, when I know the
viewership's going to be down, when I
know the hype is going to be down, cuz
this is the time where everyone here can
actually win. Because it's just 10% of
us versus the 90% in the future, you
know?
>> Yeah. Yeah, I think the biggest thing,
you know, with you is like the accuracy
um when talking about some of these
tokens. And a lot of people will get
upset about it, because like you said,
they'll catch it on the way down. But
it's about right now, when no one else
is here. You know, I mean, you can't
It's like meme coins all have They all
end up in the same place, right? Retrace
60-90%, but it's about the time you have
in between that to make something,
instead of the stuff you got now that's
just pumping and dumping in 60 seconds,
you know what I mean? So,
uh we need that holding culture back.
And I think that people like you cuz of
the accuracy, you know?
>> Yeah, I mean, the thing is, how accurate
do you need to be to
just anticipate a like two or three
memes that are going to hit a billion
plus market cap? You know, every cycle
there's going to be some memes that are
going to hit a billion plus, and I don't
think it's that out there crazy to
anticipate what that's going to be.
There are some memes, like, for example,
Brett. It had such a clear, strong case.
You had speculation of a Coinbase
airdrop. You had two uh
200 million Coinbase users. You had the
case of, "Hey, if even 10% of Coinbase's
users are on the base chain, and you
know, if you have X amount of users who
get $10 on average, $50 on average, $100
on average, or if they do a base airdrop
that's $40 worth, and people are getting
10% of that, that's 40 uh $4 billion of
liquidity that can go into memes. You
know, it was just such a strong case
there, and you have the same case on Ton
now this cycle. You have very strong
case on Troll. Like, you There are
strong cases out there, and there are so
many weak [snorts] cases. So, okay,
first thing, avoid the weak cases. Avoid
the weak coins. Avoid the weak ideas
that you know, like, nobody is ever
going to bid that at a billion. And now,
automatically, you're left with, like,
1% of coins that ever have a chase a a
case or even any valid case of trading
at a billion plus market cap. I really
don't think it's that hard, man.
But, I mean,
>> That's also cuz you're like, you're also
a stud at it, right? I mean, I've been
in this space for 6 years, and I still
I've done well. I've been investing in
good coins. A lot of them are like stuff
that you tweet about. Like, all right,
well, I I kind of just like
not just
it like I I I do have people I look at
them like, all right, these guys have
had great calls, but identifying winners
I mean, for you, it's easy cuz you're a
pro at it, right? Just like the
carpenter that you said, him installing
something in your house, a desk, is easy
cuz he's a pro at it, right? It's tough
for us. So, not everybody is into this
meme coin space like you are or we are
tapped in on a daily basis. How do you
identify the winners? You talked about
Ponky, Reedu, Bobo, Brett. How exactly
like, what do you look at? What do you
look for? When you're looking at a token
right now in 2026, a meme coin to invest
in, what are you looking for that says,
"Hey, this actually has potential to be
a billion-dollar runner?"
>> So, the first thing is you have to
understand how how did this meme wave
start? You know, this last meme wave.
Pepe went to 1.6 billion out of nowhere.
And then from there, every other meme
coin can be like, "Well, if Pepe hit 1.6
billion, we deserve to be half the
market cap of Pepe." And the next coin
down the list will be like, "Well, we
deserve to be half the market cap of
that coin." And the next one will be,
"We deserve to be half or fourth of that
one." And so, everything derives its
value as a comparison of what's on top
or what's bigger than it. Right? So, the
first thing you want to find where's
value is what's the number one thing of
anything, right? Whether it's the number
one shoe brand, number one beverage like
Coca-Cola or whatever it is, whether
it's the number one whatever. In this
case, I look for the number one meme on
each blockchain that I'm bullish on the
chain, that I'm bullish on the narrative
around the chain where I can see a lot
of optimism building around it cuz I
know that if a chain does well, it's
kind of like the the memes or the tokens
on it basically have steroids cuz you
know, if time when when ETH went up,
right? Uh to $4,800
in 2021,
people are buying the ETH, which is
pushing the ETH price up, then they're
taking that ETH and then they're buying
the meme coin like SHIB on Ethereum. So,
you have like double double bullish
price action because basically it's
driving the price of ETH up. Now, the
liquidity pool is paired in ETH, right?
SHIB is paired with ETH. So, whenever
the value rises of Ethereum, the USD
value of that pool also rises because
once again, the pool is measured in ETH
and the the USD price of the ETH goes
up, so that automatically makes the pool
value greater between SHIB and ETH. So,
even if you know, there's not that many
buys, but just simply because the chain
is doing well, the market cap can rise
with let's say net neutral buys and
sells, the market cap in USD can rise
alone without any buys. Now, if you have
a token that goes up 10x, you're
basically getting like 10x the buy
pressure, or not 10x the buy pressure,
but you're getting like 10x the market
cap because the pair is once again
measured in USD and the USD value goes
up 10x. So, that's how a 100 million
market cap on TON today can be a billion
market cap on TON later when the price
of TON goes up 10x. So, it's kind of
like having the wind in your sails. You
get double bullishness. That's why I
would pick a chain that you're
optimistic on and you see a future for.
>> Yeah, and on that on that note, too,
right? What we saw last cycle, it's like
everyone that bought and this is why
Solana had such a meme coin bull run.
People were buying Solana at eight
bucks, 20 bucks, 50 bucks, 70 bucks. It
ran to 290 bucks. They're up so much on
their initial investment that they have
excess capital that they can just invest
in any [__] meme coin that comes out,
right? And the same thing will happen
this cycle with ETH, with TON, with Sui,
the same thing will happen. Uh what
chains are you most bullish on? I guess
top three chains. What in 2026 and
moving forward, what are the top three
blockchains you're bullish on this cycle
when it comes to meme coins?
>> Yeah, so TON is
it's the same setup as Base last cycle.
So, I think TON has to be number one.
That's like the That's where you can
1,000x, you know, that's where you can
100x, 500x easiest because TON has the
best case out of any layer one right now
to 10x, in my opinion, you know? So,
once again, that's having the wind in
your sails, if that's the correct way to
say it, you know? Automatically it's in
your favor.
So, TON number one, but that's where
after that, dude, honestly, I don't
really care too much about 99.9% of the
chains, as I'm sure most people don't.
Like, you know, go down the list of
these chains. Whatever chains that like
number 70, 150, 280th chain, you know,
like no one cares about them. So, TON is
where it's close enough to the top where
it's like it's able to enter straight
into the top, you know, it's like right
on the edge of it. So,
>> So, why why are you why are you so
bullish? You know, you just mentioned
that TON is the number one blockchain
for meme coins this cycle. What exactly
is TON doing that makes you so bullish?
>> So, obviously, every blockchain has
pretty much the same problem almost,
which is, okay, you have a blockchain,
but you have no users, right? So,
Cardano,
they hit 80 billion market cap, but they
have no users. Uh go down the list, 99%
of these chains, they have no users. So,
TON,
you know, being backed by Telegram,
already having a billion Telegram users,
and in Telegram, they have the Telegram
wallet, and they have other ways to
integrate people directly into the
blockchain without people even noticing
they're on some blockchain. So, that's
one of the biggest bull cases is that
people naturally could be buying memes
on TON without actually going through
the friction of getting onto some
blockchain out there.
Straight from their Telegram.
>> I want to show everyone not many people
know that. When you go to Telegram,
right? A billion people use it, you go
to your settings, you scroll down,
literally right here, you have a
Telegram wallet. So, a billion people
already have access to a Telegram TON
wallet in their Telegram app, and they
don't even know it yet. Imagine when
they send that push notification and
alert people that, hey, you can now buy
TON and TON meme coins directly in your
Telegram wallet. Like, what's that going
to do for TON memes
>> It might not even be that notification.
The notification that people might be
getting is, hey, you've been using
Telegram for 1 year. So,
congratulations, you've been using
Telegram for 1 year. We're putting $10
of TON into your wallet. And then a guy
who's used it for 2 years, hey,
congratulations for being a loyal
Telegram
$50 in your wallet today. And now these
people who maybe didn't have a reason to
use the wallet before, now they're
already in. They're already a user on
the blockchain. They already have
capital ready to go put into a meme on
the chain, and turn 50 to a thousand.
So, that adds up over a billion users,
and that adds up if, you know, even if
only 10% of those users are going to get
$50 in TON, for example, that's still a
freak ton of money. That's like $5
billion, right? 100 million users times
50 bucks, it's like $5 billion, right?
Of liquidity. And so, those are what
Those are the things that you want to
look for in memes. It's It's not about
what's happening today, it's about
what's going to happen in the future, or
some things don't even need to happen.
They just need to be
something that other people can see
happening or speculate on, right? Cuz
you know how many times there's been a
blockchain or some project, and it drops
incredible news, but that's the top. Cuz
by the time the news hits, a lot of
times,
you know, the market is efficient, it's
already captured the bulk of the move,
you know? And once the the news hits,
that's that is it, you know?
So, a lot of people though, what they do
is they rush in and they buy the news
once it's already happened. The truth
is, there's insiders who buy before
news, there's people who are smart who
buy before, you know, well in advance
that are then selling once the news
finally hits. So, there's all these
efficient people in the market far
before you ever heard about that news.
So, if you're one of the people rushing
after the news,
it can work sometimes, but a lot of
times that can also be a top. Now,
that's not to say, for example, one
thing a lot of people tell me is like,
"Oh, Binance just listed the coin,
that's surely the top." And it's like,
"Well, it depends." Cuz sometimes
Binance can list a coin at the bottom,
sometimes they can list in the middle of
its run, and sometimes they can list at
the top of the run. So, to blindly take
a little catalyst like that and think
that that automatically means that it's
a top is also kind of flawed logic as
well.
>> I agree. And when it comes to the TON,
dude, interesting run, right? So, TON
launched the the Open Foundation back in
2021. Roddy, we were streaming every day
during this time when TON went on an
incredible run. It went up to $7, $8,
and then nothing really bad happened.
for those that are in the crypto space
and were on Twitter. Pavel Durov, he
like went on a private jet, landed in
France. They threw him in jail for 3
weeks. That was the catalyst that caused
TON to crash. The fact that they wrongly
threw Pavel Durov, the CEO of Telegram,
into prison for 2 or 3 weeks. He was
fighting for freedom of speech and that
caused TON to go all the way down right
around a dollar. Rodney, I mean, my
thoughts like usually that's a good
catalyst, right? If someone that you
support that's fighting for freedom of
speech gets thrown in jail. Usually you
support it, but what we saw in 2024 is
that it actually caused TON to go from
$8 down to a dollar in 2025 and 2026.
>> Yeah, you know, it's just news and
emotions. It reminds me of that one time
when Elon Musk went on the Joe Rogan
show and smoked a little bit of weed and
Tesla stock sold off like crazy. Like
just news and emotions causes people to
sell off what the market we could say
runs on. But you know, to go back to you
know, Pavel, you know, really Telegram's
like the last line of defense when it
comes to just us being able to like
communicate on a social media app
without the government
behind some sort of backdoor. I mean, we
saw people get exposed WhatsApp,
Facebook, even like Signal, which was
supposed to be this big privacy app. So,
you know, Pavel's you know, the reason
why TON I think in my opinion is so
bullish is cuz one, you know, Telegram
and crypto just go hand in hand. So,
them coming together is great. And I'm
glad he's coming out and actually
supporting
the chain, you know, whether he didn't
do it before because of political
reasons or whatever, but it's
>> good to see him come out and support the
TON ecosystem.
>> I think we have a
I don't know if we want to segue to the
the next topic, Troll.
Troll, it's already my Freudian slip.
Okay, Crash. I know you said that you
made a good point recently. You said
that what's hot now doesn't mean or what
was hot then doesn't mean it's going to
be hot now. And it kind of reminds me of
the switch we had from Ethereum tokens
to Solana tokens, right? And Pepe's
really like the last big you know,
Ethereum token we had. Solana was hot in
the beginning. We had Bonk, with some
nice holders, some runners. Then we had
the celebrity token meta. Then we had um
pump fund, and then we had a president
launching a a Solana token. And really
Solana's gotten this bad reputation. But
Chris, I haven't seen you post a ticker
in a minute. And recently, and you know,
I'm involved in the community, I've been
seeing you talk a lot about troll. You
don't really come out and post a lot of
cash tags. So, talk to us about troll uh
and really, in my opinion, changing the
perception on Solana and kind of
reviving it.
>> Yeah, so with troll it has IP rights.
And that's a huge advantage on Solana,
the chain where there's 20 [__]
versions of every damn coin. Right? If
you try to do any coin on that chain,
there's 20 other versions saying, "Well,
our contract was first." "Well, our
contract has a better community." Or
"Our contract is not racist." And stuff
like this. They they find every freaking
reason imaginable. So, it's impossible
to go up when you're diluting liquidity,
not just amongst a million meme coins,
but also amongst 20 versions of the same
coin. With troll, nobody can do that.
You can't dispute it. You can't fight
it. It's on Coinbase. It has IP. Get
[__] Get trolled. You know, you have
no chance. So, in in in a sea full of
coins
that have to compete with 20 other
versions of themselves, which those, you
know, versions of yourselves, they're
[__] because you're also a [__] coin,
you know, you have troll that just
stands out and it's it's such a
high-caliber meme like that can be up
there if you made a Mount Rushmore of
memes, troll is on there. I don't care
if you want to dispute me if it's the
number one meme, but if you made the
Mount Rushmore of memes, it's on there.
If if you say no, you you you know, just
get out get out of here, bro. I'm not
talking to you. So, yeah, it that's the
thing. Mount Rushmore of memes. Well,
let's think about it. In crypto, that's
Doge, that's Pepe.
Okay? Mount Rushmore, there's two faces
left. Troll, there you go. It has to be
there. It's inevitable. The market knows
this. Now that there's official IP coin
on Coinbase, it's only a matter of time
until the market prices that, or should
I say re-prices that Mount Rushmore
coin, you know?
>> So, let's talk about it. It's currently
at a a hundred nine million dollar
market cap, right? And I mean, let's
just look at the chart. The troll for
everybody that's at home, guys, this is
troll uh that Crash is talking about,
launched on April Wow, 4/20, 2025.
Uh ran up to a it looks like $250
million market cap uh towards the peak
of the bull run in 2025. October,
started to fall down below a $20 million
market cap. Had a little bit of a run
here again, right? A strong run at a
$109 million market cap. Look, I
remember very, very, very vividly back
in 2022, Rodney and I were streaming.
This is like
right after Bonk launched, we saw Wif,
we saw Mog. And this is 2022, so keep in
mind, this is pretty similar to where
we're at right now in 2026. We just had
all-time highs of a $69,000 Bitcoin in
2021. It's like February, March 2022, we
got tokens like Bonk, like Wif, like Mog
starting to launch. They're at $25
million market cap, $50 million market
cap. Ponky launches, $100 million market
cap. All of those tokens, I remember
thinking too, like
it's already at a hundred million dollar
market cap, bro. That's so high, right?
All of those tokens that I just
mentioned, most of those went to the
billions, right? So, Crash, if someone's
looking at this today and they're
looking at their chart and they're going
they have like this Solana meme coin
culture, like, "Ah, it's a hundred nine
million dollar market cap, man. It's too
late." Earlier this month in May, it was
at a $20 million market cap. I saw it
then. I should have bought it then. For
anyone that's looking at troll today on
May 22nd saying, "A hundred million
dollar market cap is too high." What
would be your answer to them?
>> Okay. My answer would be to actually
start with one simple question.
Do you agree? Right, I would ask this
person, do you agree that troll belongs
on the Mount Rushmore of memes?
Oh, you do? Okay. So, let's look who
else is on there. Doge, 80 billion.
Pepe, 11 billion. How is troll at a 100
million market cap high? Right? Becomes
very obvious. The thing is, 100 million
seems high if you're comparing it to
junk. And it's extremely low if you're
on the Mount Rushmore. Right? So, that
it's that simple, you know? You just got
to know what kind of coin are you in?
Are you in a shitcoin? Are you in a top
four meme coin of all time? Right? And
troll is going to be a top four meme
coin of all time. I believe it's going
to be the number one meme on Solana. I
think it's going to flip fart coin, it's
going to flip bonk, it's going to flip
doge coin, it's going to flip every
single meme coin on Solana.
>> Every
>> Every single meme coin on Solana.
>> Okay.
>> It's only a matter of time. Because
that's the thing, none of these coins,
you know, above troll in market cap
currently
uh are going to be able to justify that
market cap compared to how easily troll
can justify a higher market cap than
them. So, once again, you got to
realize, okay, so why troll now? Well,
because there never was an official
troll with IP rights. It was a bunch of
contracts fighting over, well, we're the
troll or this is the troll. And so, you
can't give your confidence to the troll,
a troll coin, right? Because, well, how
do I know this is the one? But now you
know it's the one. And this hasn't been
a reality in the market for a long time.
That's also why I believe it's pretty
damn easy to make money in crypto
because the market is inefficient. It is
inefficient in memes. And um and so,
yeah, this this reality of troll being
the official troll, like how long has
this lasted, right? Not long enough for
the market to catch on fully and fully,
you know, have a a bull cycle to reprice
it to where it belongs. So, it's not a
to me it's not a question. Troll will be
a multi-billion dollar coin. The
question then is, okay, if you're
sitting there today, are you someone who
thinks, well, 100 million is high, or do
you sit there and think, well, I don't
have time to wait 6 months to a year, or
I don't have time to wait until the next
bull run that truly happens where, you
know, these things go vertical. Because
some some people they might say, oh, I
would love to make a 100 X, but ask
them, are you willing to wait 12 months?
And now, okay, they they'll tell you
they are, but their actions are
different because actually they get
bored in the meantime and instead of
holding that easy 100 X, they end up
going and doing something else. So.
>> Yep.
Yeah. I mean, they they go to pump fund,
you know, and get rugged. But for anyone
that's looking at a chart thinking it's
too high, so you just got to understand
where we're at in the markets, right?
Now, this was like October 2025, I'd be
like, yeah, you know, it looks like
crypto's topping, we're probably going
to go into a bear market, but they're
literally Troll is building in the bear
market, 109 million dollars. I mean,
this chart looks incredibly healthy
after having an all-time high. It looks
like over a 270 million dollar market
cap back in August. Uh and for all the
reasons that Crash mentioned, it might
be time to add some Troll to the
portfolio, right? The Mount Rushmore of
meme coins. So, you And for those that
are at home right now, I just had up the
top meme coin charts here.
In order to become the number one meme
coin on Solana today, it just needs to
flip Pudgy Penguins, which is a top 75
token trading at a 571 million dollar
market cap. So, about a 5.7, if you
will, X away from doing it. Crash, is
this a Is this a token that you think
can actually get into the top 10 of meme
coins maybe during this bear market? Is
this going to have to wait for more
retail investors and more people to kind
of come back into the meme coin and
crypto space?
>> So, I don't know what's the ranking
right now, like number 20 or something?
Number 15?
>> for you. It's probably
Uh it's probably like top 30, it looks
like, almost. Yeah, it's like So, it
like I mean, if I was to show you like
I'll show you these right here, like and
you can tell me how undervalued you
think it is, right? So, top 10's right
around SPX, we have Dog with it's
probably 15.
>> a lot of these are [__] like
completely.
>> Pepe Pepe?
>> No one knows what that is, right? It's
just some
>> There's probably some some Chinese cabal
manipulating. That's got like 99% of
that [__] Same thing with like banana
for scale or cheems and these other
stuff. I promise you, no one none of us
know what these coins are.
>> Skydog, bro, I know what the [__] meme
coin is. What is meme coin?
>> Supposedly it's the number two biggest
meme in the world. No one even holds it,
right? So it's just manipulated
trash, you know? No one no one cares
about this stuff. So I think if you take
out those fake coins, right? These are
probably like Chinese manipulated scams.
Uh you're probably already at number 20.
I think we reprice during the bear
market and probably take over a number
another five to 10 spots. So we're
probably going to be sitting at number
10 here soon.
And then
I think honestly, you never you just
never know when is that crazy running
going to happen. Is it going to happen
tomorrow or is it going to happen in
three months from now? Um and it's just
a matter of waiting off until that
moment. And it's going to come. And that
moment, once again,
um Pepe had its moment where it went
from zero to 1.6 billion.
>> Mhm.
>> The spotlight it it kind of
not dies off, right? But cools off, goes
from 1.6 billion all the way down to
250, 300 million market cap. Then from
there goes to 11 billion. So I think
you're not just going to have one
moment, you're going to have multiple
moments. The thing is that yeah, the you
know, whenever
you know, it pulls back, everything
pulls back 80 to 90% before it goes way
higher. That's why I tell people, when
you're up double, sell half. If you're
up triple, sell a third. If you're up
quadruple, sell a quarter. If you're up
10x, sell a tenth. Get your initial
capital back. You can always put it back
in if it dips, you know? And that will
actually lead you to if you put in your
initial capital back in on a 80 to 90%
dip ever, you know, you get a way better
entry, you get a bigger position, and
you're just stress-free. It's easier to
manage it. It's easier to support the
chart whenever, you know, that time
comes to spark the next run. So, but the
thing is I think we're in the middle of
one run right now. Obviously, Bitcoin
has taken a dump right now, so it makes
it a little harder, but overall, I think
we all know, okay, so we're in the
middle of a run right now. Keyword a
run, not the run or the next runs.
There's going to be future runs that
make this one look like an ant. You
know, this one This is going to be one
of the tiniest runs that you are going
to zoom out on the chart later, and
you're going to have to go back and like
zoom in on this little moment to find
this. Truly, because whenever you're at
10 billion, this literally you're going
to I'm telling you, you're going to have
to zoom in and find this moment again.
So, it's just knowing where you are as
well.
>> Exactly. And I'll I'll show you an
example of that real quick. Sorry,
Ronnie, but I'll I'll show you
Pepe. I remember and and all of us that
were here back in 2023, remember Pepe
ran into a 1.6
>> in like a week.
>> billion.
>> billion-dollar market cap. This was the
all-time high. This was insane, right?
It went from 200 million, 300, 500, like
you literally cannot even see it, right?
And then you look at what I mean, you
look at what happened. Just one of the
most incredible runs. And then you're
talking about an 11-billion-dollar
market cap. This is what Crash is
saying. So, right now, when you look at
the troll chart, we're right here,
right? 100 million is nothing. I mean,
it's a 10x away from a billion. It's a
100x away from Pepe numbers. And Crash
is saying he's not saying it's going to
get to an 11-billion-dollar market cap,
but he's saying that it does belong up
there in the top spots with Pepe and
Doge. Crash, you got to ask you, you
name
three
Mount Rushmore tokens. There's a fourth
spot. You're talking Mount Rushmore,
talking presidents, is Trump coin your
number four? What's going to be the
number four? Maybe it hasn't released
yet.
>> I think it would probably be on TON. Um
with because man, with TON having a if
TON does a 10x, it's going to be very
hard for TON meme there to not go to
two, three billion at least, you know?
Think about this base, right? Base had
no token, had no airdrop, Brett hit 2.3
billion. So, what happens when you have
a token like TON that actually goes up
10x? When it whenever that happens,
first of there's a lot of institutions,
whales, and big money in TON that will
be up a lot and they can easily take
some off and put into memes. But also
just regular people that are holding TON
then are up 10x and they can rotate some
of that extra purchasing power liquidity
into memes. It just creates a way more
explosive setup than even base had in my
opinion. And we saw how explosive it was
on base. So, I think you're going to
have base's run on steroids. And so many
freaking people love to be like, "Well,
I bought bread at 2.3 billion." Okay,
did you buy it at 30 million, right? I
bet you if you bought it at 30 million,
your entire outlook on meme coins would
be completely different. You would be a
very happy person. Yeah. But that's the
thing. You try to tell these people uh
later
whenever it's too late. But now is the
time when it's not too late. Now is the
time where okay, you have that moment on
base, right? Where you're at 30 million
market cap on a TON meme and you have
that. And but no, I'm going to have to
hear [__] when stuff hits two, three,
five billion market cap all about how
some guy bought at five billion market
cap and it's my fault now. But that's
why I'm like, I'm here. And people are
like, "Fucking scammer. Why are you here
in the bear market when you're trying to
push up memes whenever the market's not
bullish?" It's because that's the time,
bro. That's the time you actually can
make a 100x. Once everything is super
bullish and everyone's going crazy and
the trade is consensus and everyone's
rushing into TON memes, yes, you're
going to have a window there of probably
30 to 90 days of just incredible. You
wake up, your your portfolio is up 100%.
You wake up the next day it's up another
100%. That also isn't going to last
forever. Once again, that that can last
30 to 90 days, you know, but yeah, this
is the time where you got to plant your
seeds and walk away and just be chill
with it. Be confident, know like, hey, I
got the number one meme on Ton. I got
the number two meme on Ton and just
reduce it down to the simplest form. Do
you think Ton will never have an a a
meme coin that crosses a billion market
cap? I think that's a really bad bet to
make. I think that's a really bad stance
to take. If I had to go to sleep at
night knowing if I had to go into like
eternal slumber, right? I'm sleeping for
for years and years and and the deal is
you only wake up again if you're correct
about this. Choose your side. Does Ton
ever have a billion-dollar meme coin or
no? I'm going to say yes. I don't want
to be asleep forever. I don't want to
lose that deal. I'm picking a
billion-dollar plus meme Ton for sure is
going to happen, you know? So, if you
can truly sleep at night with peace like
that and confidently know that, then
it's only a matter of time. You know
that the the the dominoes will fall into
place. The the attention will come. It
it may not be here this moment. Everyone
may not be hyped out of hyped up about
crypto, but you know it's going to fall
into place cuz if you're correct about
that future outcome that a meme hits a
billion plus on this chain, everything
falls into place. I want people to
understand that. When you know you're
right or when you can confidently hold a
stance
and sleep on it, you know that these are
the best positions you want to take in
the market. Not little scalps, not
little trades where you know like, okay,
I might be right, I might not be right.
No, you want to go for me, that's how I
make the biggest amount is always just
when you know, when you know it, bro,
you know? And I know it. I know it and I
know so many know it. We're going to
have a billion-dollar meme on this
chain, so what is there to lose sleep
over, bro? It's just a matter of time.
>> You got me you got me fired up. I feel
it, bro. I feel the conviction. And
look, I think so I was at the gym,
right? And this is probably something
that a lot of people in this stream are
feeling. If you
I go to the gym every day, Rodney. You
know this [__] Come on, son. But I was
in the gym and I was talking to my guy.
My guy, we're doing a stream tonight
with Crash and Rodney. And the guy's
like, "Dude, don't even talk to me about
meme coins. Like I'm I'm focused on like
real world shit." He's a big crypto
investor, big meme coin trader. But what
happened is is he's burnt out because
the last cycle, right? What happened
with the
Someone's calling me. What happened with
the the Trump meme coin and everything
from last cycle, a lot of people were
burnt out of understandably so. It was
somewhat of a tough cycle. But Crash,
you mentioned TON uh
billion-dollar meme coins on TON. This
reminds me of something I'm going to
show you this. It's a post from Pavel
Durov. This reminds me I remember
vividly it was like 2023 or June of
2024. I was in Bowie. I was still making
videos and Coinbase was like
subliminally tweeting bread if you will,
right? Like kind of soft shilling bread.
They're like, "The Coinbase wallet is
now live." And in there on the main page
on their tweet was bread on base. I want
to see Rodney maybe your thoughts on
this.
Lock the bots.
Let me Someone's calling me. Let me put
my phone on do not disturb. First, no
calling me during a live stream with
Crash and Rodney. What the hell is wrong
with you? Now,
I want to see this Am I crazy? And I've
been I've been talking about a token on
TON called Utya, a meme coin. I don't
know if you guys have seen it. Rodney
has. But am I crazy to think that Pavel
is soft shilling this meme coin? Let me
play the video here. Pavel Durov, the
founder of Telegram, he says, "Your
Telegram inbox can now run itself.
Assign a bot to read and reply for for
you with granular control over its
permissions and chat access." Actually a
really cool feature. But look, he's
showing Bert Bertram, who Is that Murad?
Kind of looks like Murad. Murad got a
new job. He didn't sell meme coins, so
now he's doing brand ambassadorships for
Telegram. But look, you have your
profile, you have your wallet. So
everybody has a wallet. Like look, the
wallet could be down below save like it
could be down further. They literally
are putting the wallet second, bro.
They're pushing this [__] hard. And then
look, everything Pavel Durov does,
everything Telegram does, is they they
know what they're doing, right? So, this
is a 9-second video. You got uh Timur
Marat at the top. And then once you go
down, you can see once you click chat on
mission, who do we see? Who's that? This
to me looks like the Uchi Duck, which is
the top meme coin on TON right now, uh
which just ran to a 60 million-dollar
market cap and is trading at a 29
million-dollar market cap today. But to
me, I feel like Pavel and the Telegram
team and the TON Foundation, they know
what they're doing. They understand
that, "Hey, we want to build our meme
coin ecosystem. We want to get as many
people into the TON Foundation and the
TON ecosystem as possible." And every
single developer, no matter who you are,
Sui, Solana, Ethereum, probably not
Cardano cuz they did a terrible job,
they understand that memes are going to
be bring people onto their blockchain
more than anything.
>> Yes.
>> And I don't know, Rodney, but to me, it
looks like Pavel Durov knows what he's
doing when he is showing this Uchi Duck
in that 9-second video and also showing
the wallet there that he's posting on
his X.
>> You know, you you talked about uh you
compared it to Coinbase and Brett, but
hopefully someone getting an echo.
But um
>> Yeah, I'm on a call here.
>> Oh, good. You compared it to Coinbase
and Brett, but hopefully they don't bust
a Coinbase and never ever mention the
top meme coin on their layer two, which
is crazy, by the way. But that's what
meme coins are about, man. We're start
We're starting to read between the
lines, you know what I mean? And it's
hard not to talk about something that's
kind of the official mascot of the
network, you know, the number one meme
coin that everybody knows about on TON.
>> I mean, everybody go to Telegram now and
just like send a 3-minute video to your
saved messages and tell me the the image
that pops up. I'll do it right now live
on stream so you guys can see it. So, I
literally before I saw Uchi, I'm like,
"Where have I seen this [__]
beautiful cute duck before?" And I'm
like, "Oh, every time I upload a
5-minute video to my editors, the Uchi
Duck is the one that's there loading."
Like I'll do it live on stream so you
guys you guys can see it.
I'm going to send it to myself.
>> Jake has the rubber duck in his ice
bath.
>> In my ice bath. I did have a Trump
rubber ducky, too. Ready? So, I'm
sending a video to myself. Let me go
ahead and send it this way.
I'll show you guys what it looks like,
but it is
it's pretty crazy.
No, I got to upload it a different way.
Uh it's like this. You got to go from
your photos. For those that are watching
at home, go from your photos. I want to
do a live on stream. I'm going to hit
Telegram, Rodney.
It's preparing it. Watch this. This
shit's crazy. So, like
it's right in front of our eyes. And a
lot of time it is, right? Like Base had
Brett right in front of millions of
eyeballs, and I feel like Ton is doing
the same thing with Uchiya. So, let's go
ahead and send this to Rodney. And who
do we have here, guys?
I'm sending a video, like a
a minute-long video. I know it's a
little bit blurry, but you can see you
have the Uchiya duck that is there for
everybody to see. Pretty crazy [__]
Rodney.
>> Nice little Nice little plug there, huh?
>> Nice little plug. I mean, I think I And
look, that's just my thoughts. It's at a
$30 million market cap today. I think
that Uchiya will be trading in the
billions.
>> You know, it's a good question to ask,
you know, Crash. You know, Crash? Well,
we've seen a lot really, you know, in
the bear market. First, I want to say
that everybody who's in the the crypto
space right now, congrats. A lot of
people gave up. I'm going to look at the
same story literally printed 4 years
about 4 years ago about how Coinbase is
cutting staff and the down This is
Everybody forgets, right? Everybody has
a short memory in the crypto space. This
[__] happens every 4 years. So many
people have given up on meme coins,
talking about stocks now. More power to
you. They just think meme coins are
dead. Um and you know, recently the
Solana Foundation came out and talked
about how meme coins don't define
Solana, which is crazy if you think
about pump fun. But I want to get your
opinion on just how important to meme
coins are to like an ecosystem in
general.
>> Yeah, I mean, it's the main main main
main attraction for most people in the
bull run. So, we can ignore it and act
like it's not.
You can act like you're all about the
tech and stuff and cool, go for it. Be
all about the tech, but also just
acknowledge the simple fact that bro,
like half of the volume and attention
does come from memes in all of crypto,
you know? So, yeah, I just think it's
disingenuous to to say that memes don't
make up a good [clears throat] bit of
crypto, right? So.
>> I 100% agree. I don't know if you guys
saw this too, little segue here, but it
looks like pro crypto Kevin Warsh has
officially been sworn in as the Fed
chair. So, no more too late Jerome
Powell. Kevin Warsh officially has been
sworn in and guys, I went through his
portfolio. Not only does Kevin Warsh
own some crypto, he owns over nine
figures. So, over a hundred million
dollars worth of crypto and he currently
holds in his portfolio Ronnie, over 30
different cryptocurrency projects.
That's like 18 more than I hold. So,
this guy not only is a new Federal
Reserve chair, not only does he have
nine figures in crypto, the guy is kind
of a degen. He's got 30 cryptos he's
holding. Like I can't even keep track of
30. So, we now have too late Jerome
Powell, he's now fired. Kevin Warsh, a
crypto
advocate, a crypto proponent, a crypto
holder of 30 different cryptos and nine
figures is now the Fed chair. Big news
here on E-Masterclass right now. That's
big news for cryptocurrency if I have to
say so myself.
>> Yeah, huge news. Obviously, you know,
Trump wanted somebody in there who's
going to be more pro-Trump and less pro
everything else. I honestly don't think
Jerome Powell was doing a bad job. He
was not. He got inflation down from nine
to three. That's nuts, right?
But,
big daddy gets what big daddy wants. Big
daddy Trump wants a guy who's going to
be do you know, give monetary policies
that are going to help whatever his
economic agenda is. So, shout out to him
and pump our bags, baby, you know? Bear
gang is gone. [__] he cut the he cut
the head off the snake, man. Trump is
just it's a wild wild west now. I love
it.
>> I'm going to show you what he owns real
quick and then we'll segue, but
right here Kevin O'Leary owns exposure
to more than 20 different cryptocurrency
related projects. Solana, optimism,
lightning network, compound,
Uchiya. Wow, you don't No, I'm just
kidding.
And he he's invested in in in companies
like Polymarket, Polychain, Flashnet,
Zero Gravity, DSo, Blast, Lighter. Like
dude, he is in this space. Speaking of
Polymarket, if I was Jerome Powell, like
there was literally every time he had
his Fed chair meeting, there was a a
Polymarket like market for will Jerome
Powell start off with good afternoon?
Like if I'm him, I'm putting 100k on
that every time and saying
>> Crazy.
>> Good afternoon. I mean Jerome Powell. He
would talk like this a little bit and
like he would just say that inflation's
going down and we're doing everything
that we can to work with the president,
but tariffs aren't helping.
>> I'm glad he's gone. Hopefully Kevin has
a little bit more energy, a little bit
more high T, maybe 1,100. Crash, if you
had it, let me show you a picture. You
got to guess
You got to guess this giga Chad's
testosterone. And keep in mind he's a
little bit old, but look, the guy's a
good looking guy, good good looking guy,
owns
what is it? 100 million in crypto. What
kind of T is coming from Kevin Warsh,
Crash?
>> [laughter]
>> You guessed right on the T. No pun
intended.
>> 600.
>> Yeah, I get 655 vibes, you know.
But looks like in his later years, like
look, looks like he's kind of got some
more T, more more swag as he gets a
little bit older here, especially now
that he's the Fed chair. So
I get like 550 here, you know. We need
to get him on some TRT or some peptides.
But I got to segue now, Crash, cuz I saw
a tweet the other day. First off,
there was an account, it's
I think it
I'll pull it up right here. So
Market Bubble, which is a new show on X,
they posted the top 25 of Crypto
Twitter. I looked through the list,
there's some guys, Kobe I think is
great,
Thread Guy, Jeff, Trader Main. All these
guys are great. We'll talk about number
nine in a second, Crash. Gainsey, Jewish
friend, Rasmus, Jewish A A of good guys,
right?
A lot of people are missing. To not
include Crash Clay on this list is
absolute blasphemy, right? To not
include CZ Binance on this list is
blasphemy.
>> But he's not an influencer.
>> [laughter]
>> He's technically an influencer. I mean,
he was bull posting some memes whether
he said he was or not.
>> Yeah, he he didn't know.
>> The BNB season he was bull Aster, he's
the number one influencer for Aster. Are
you kidding me? He's the one that
tweeted about it first at 10 cents. He
put in $2 he's the number one
influencer. But I got to show a tweet.
So Crash, first off, you should be on
this list. I would say top top three in
my opinion. But it's not my list. Maybe
the master class needs to make a list,
an accurate list, a real list. Uh, but
Crash, I I went through the comments and
I saw a comment that you made. So,
number nine is Jesse Pollak from
Coinbase, right? From Base.
>> what I said was true.
Oh, okay. Okay.
>> Yeah, no. I I have it pulled up here.
I'm pretty sure that he is uh
he's the he's on the actual like C team
of Coinbase. And this was the tweet that
you said you said
you said
>> Can you read it out loud specifically
the second word from that?
>> I'll read it for you. You said, "Jesse
Faglak at number nine crying face.
Somebody must have really liked him in
his bikini.
And he had to have thrown the greater
pizza the greatest pizza party ever.
Ain't no
ain't no party like a Jesse party.
What's the what what's up with the
bikini though? Is there something going
on with the bikini? Well, he's
explaining add this to the Yeah, there
it is. Well, he Well, he he's explaining
the story.
>> What is this? This is AI, bro. That's
AI.
>> [laughter]
>> You know, you're assuming it's AI.
But I would assume there's been even
worse things in this image we've seen
that have went down to get onto that
ninth spot of that list.
>> We met
>> I don't even want I don't even want to
imagine what's happened to get to the
ninth spot of that list. Let's not even
talk about it, I would say, bro. This
image is horrific enough.
>> Well, let's talk about it. Let's talk
about it, you know?
This image Is this AI? It has to be like
dude, Chat GPT is getting good. There's
no way he's wearing a bikini eating
pizza taking a selfie like that.
No way, dude. No
>> Is that real?
>> You guys have a little bit too much
faith in the guy that launched like
hundreds of creator coins and rug them,
I would say.
>> That's that's they went from USDC to
point of sale to straight to Zora and
[__]
what is it
[__] whatever tokens in a heartbeat.
What was up with that?
>> Pretty [__]
>> It was, bro. For someone I've never
launched a token in my life like to see
them like the Coinbase the gold center
and it was with the whole meta though
like everybody on pump fun too like Alex
Becker everybody launched a creator
token and just abandoned it now. The
thing with Coinbase was they launched
like 6,000. Jesse [__] literally
launched a token saying Jesse [__]
don't launch a token like [__] like
that. Like it was like he literally
launched a token every day and then just
they all went to zero. Like where did
that money go, right?
>> They say it's innovative but
it if
And and then they want to act like
they're against meme coins for a while
and then they have to act like they're
pro meme coins.
So, how are you against meme coins but
you're pro creating stupid [__] that has
zero lasting staying power, you know?
It's just dumb. It's it's all dumb. It's
all if you focus on the wrong things you
get bad results. That's ultimately what
happened. They put no focus on the top
memes or a lot of the top things that
brought so much attention to the
ecosystem. There was another AI project
on their virtuals, right? Uh which I
believe never even got listed on
Coinbase. I would have to check. May
maybe they did end up uh eventually but
you know, that was literally the biggest
AI project to come out of base I think
and got absolutely no love almost.
>> Yeah, what I noticed from Coinbase and
and you know, I worked with them for a
little bit and I worked with these good
people. They were really nice to me. But
what I noticed is they wanted the
attention of meme coins without wanting
to talk about them or mention them or at
least pay homage to them. You know, the
holier than thou like altcoin people I
mean look at a lot of the altcoins that
were like banging back in the day. They
were literally worse than some meme
coins. That's how crazy they've they've
they've they've they've fallen back.
But, the crazy thing, yeah, about just
the base ecosystem, they they wanted the
clout that memes bring, but they never
wanted to show them any love, which was
crazy to me.
>> Yeah, well, the the annoying thing is I
get so much [__] like, "Brett, hit 2.3
billion. [__] you. You suck." It's like,
"Hey, maybe we would have hit six six or
seven billion if Jesse Faglac didn't
exist."
>> Six seven?
>> Six [laughter] seven billion.
>> Why, you know? Why?
>> Why not support it?
>> It's crazy to me.
>> Every person who bought the top could
have been up 3x probably if Jesse
Faglac, uh, you know, wasn't eating
pizza in the in a bikini. But, guess
what?
I I know for a fact of the potential of
all memes on base, right? I'm not This
is not just Brett. All memes on base got
probably 50 to
30% of their actual potential due to how
he was doing [__] So, that guy is a
huge net negative for base. Anyone who
acts like he's a positive, I'm just
going to nod my head and and just try to
understand that, okay, probably we're
trying to act nice to him, so, you know,
whatever for whatever reason someone may
have or But, but if we're just being
honest or in your room talking by
yourself, you'd be like, "Yeah, that guy
is [__] [__] and, uh, all he did
was hurt base, in my opinion." And and
and you know, the the thing is, I hate
when people act like they're doing
something good. Uh, they act like
they're all this and that, but then
they're doing the complete opposite of
it, in my opinion.
>> So, righteous. That's what it is, you
know? Like virtue signaling. Like all
the people that are in there like the
23-year-old girl who's living off
daddy's money in San Francisco who like
just post black black life matters stuff
because it's like viral in San
Francisco, right? Like just virtue
signaling. Now, we met Jesse [__]
We met Jesse [__] in San Francisco. I
interviewed him for On Chain Summit. He
was cool. I think I think look and I'll
shoot it straight out. This is what I
would say if you're saying we're going
to talk about our stuff in a room or on
a live stream with 5,000 people. Guys,
shout out to everybody that's here on X,
on YouTube, on Kick. Make sure you
retweet, follow all the three
all three of us on here, but I think he
did do some stuff. Like his idea was to
bring the world on chain. I think he did
do good stuff. Like he had some good
moments with Coinbase. I covered a lot
of them in terms of like
getting people to adopt USDC, right? He
he did some good stuff within the base
ecosystem. He also did some bad stuff,
right? I mean launching 7,000 meme coins
is obviously a net negative. Not
embracing Brett and I'm pretty sure I
talked to him privately at the on chain
summit about Brett. Just like, "Yo, you
got to check this out. It's at a 1.5
billion dollar market cap. Like it's
carrying your chain. Like what's going
on?" And instead of just supporting
Brett and saying, "Yeah, we're going to
get behind this and you know, give it
some love cuz it's going to bring more
people to our chain." They ended up
launching like legitimately 700 tokens,
which is [__] stupid, right? So, I
think he did and I don't remember
everything off the top of my head. He
did do some good stuff for base. He did
some bad stuff for base.
Um and
>> Yeah, you know, at the end of the day
it's it's extremely rare you'll ever
hear me talk [__] about someone like
that. I don't like to do it, but I I
think occasionally you can save a few,
you know, the opposite of Mount
Rushmore, but put some [__] on
blast spots and he belongs one on one of
those faces for me. So, you know,
special special I don't know thanks to
him for being one of the great four
faces of shame for me this last cycle.
And and look, man, I saw someone say,
"Oh, blaming this guy for why you called
it wrong." Bro, I called Brett at 2
million market cap.
>> 1.6
>> 1.3 billion market cap, bro. If that's
calling it wrong, how what do you have
to do to be right? You need to call
something at 2 million and it goes to 80
billion? I mean, this is
absurd. It's it was objectively one of
the best calls ever in meme coins. Top
five, top three. So, if that's not a
good call, you have no idea what you're
talking about.
>> Top three. The only other one is like
Morad, right? SBX, I mean that ripped.
And then anyone else who called Shib
early, who called Pepe early? I mean
>> Yeah.
>> Like I recorded a video on Pepe at 80
million, it went to 11 billion. Like
that's a good call, but it doesn't
compare to
the 1.3 million to 2.5 billion. Like
it's But yeah, you had in my opinion
like that I can think of, I don't know
exactly when Morad called SBX, but his
conviction SBX and then your Brett calls
top two and then maybe there's You know,
there's other people who called WIF and
Bonk early, but those are the ones that
really stood out and also because you
guys did it like on public wallets, too.
I think that's what really stood out.
>> Yeah.
>> I do want to say that
>> call it, you bought it, too, right? Like
you put your money where your mouth is
and then you held. You guys are [__]
kind of crazy for holding so long, but
you held the entire time, too, right?
Which is impressive.
>> Yeah, I do want to say that Base, I
think it is one of the top layer twos
and it's usually the best layer two, but
I will say that the switch-up was crazy.
Like the switch-up from Jesse was crazy
crazy and not Brett all the way down.
But yeah, that was a goated call, you
know, I saw your post the other day and
a lot of people give a lot of people
like us [__] for like, you know,
supporting you and stuff, but keep in
mind guys, we're in the a very small
space. The accuracy it's about accuracy.
It's like it's like an NBA player with
shooting accuracy. Like the best
shooters are like 40 in the 40s, right?
Sometimes high 30s sometimes. Think Kobe
like had a shooting percentage like in
high 30s, right?
And same thing with Steph Curry, you
know, the best three-point shooter of
all time. Like it's the accuracy that
counts in the crypto. calls so many
things, but when you call a few that do
really well and a few that maybe don't
work out, I mean that's in this space,
that's a big deal. And just because you
saw it on the way down, it's nobody's
fault but yours, but now you have that
new opportunity in preparation for the
next bull run with a play like Troll,
right? Who knows how it's going to end
up, but that's
you know, it's you're kind of in the
moment. You can't see the future, you
know?
>> I think Troll hits at least 11 billion,
you know. The thing is people people are
not really There's more money in the
market than before when these coins were
hitting 5 billion plus market cap, you
know. If you think when Doge and Shib
hit 88 billion and 40 billion
Bitcoin was only around 60 60,000, you
know. Now we're at 75 78,000 at our lows
at our bad times, you know, in the down
times. So there is more money out there.
Sure more of it might be getting
allocated to some other things at the
moment, but money rotates and it flows,
you know. So right now okay, it's
flowing a little, you know, over there.
But money flows back around sometimes,
you know, especially if you have the
right narrative, you have the right
vision of where something is going to
go. So that's the thing with Ton, right?
We we all know Ton is down like 90%
almost. Uh you know, Ton memes they're
not even close to a billion market cap.
So do you have the right narrative that
can attract the money in the future? A
future rotation and and not just the
rotation, but a repositioning fully,
like a permanent repositioning of
capital onto Ton, right? It's very
different when Solana is at $8 and it's
at $240. So I think Ton right now is
like Solana at $8. And so yeah, the
money is out there, but guess what? When
Solana is at $8 was all the money in
there right away? Was it
>> Hell no.
>> No, it right it dropped from like what?
240 down to what? $4 $8, right?
>> Mhm.
>> And it goes back up again, you know. So
money once again it goes in, then it
goes out, then it goes back in, then it
goes back out, right? It just flows in
and out, but it the thing is money flows
to the right things. It doesn't flow
into the wrong things. So focus on being
right and the money is out there. It's
just a matter of when does it flow into
what you're in. And so I know it'll flow
in.
Just when?
>> Yeah, let me ask you again cuz it it
kind of got out. So you just said that
Troll currently trading at a 110 million
dollar market cap, you think it could
potentially trade above an 11 billion
dollar market cap this cycle which would
be a clean 100 x from where we're at
today on May 22nd, 2026.
>> The the question was sorry.
>> No, just that you think like just in
terms of how high troll can go. So it
cut out a little bit when you were
saying it. So I just want to make sure
that we hear you correctly, but today's
today's so
No, so today so today is May 22nd
>> When when
>> No, no, no, I'm just saying.
I'm just saying [laughter] that
today right now is May 22nd, 2026 and
I'm asking you it's at a 110 million
dollar market cap. So you just said live
on stream that you do think that we
could see troll trading above an 11
billion dollar market cap which means
everyone that sees this right now has a
chance in your opinion
to get a clean 100 x from today's
current price.
>> Yeah, everyone does I believe cuz you
went into Pepe you made a video on Pepe
when it was well below 100 million
market cap. You saw what I did. Hit 11
billion. Dogecoin millionaire, he went
in heavy into Doge at 6 cents. Not even
at a penny, not even below a penny. He
went in at 6 cents and then then it goes
to what? 60 to 70 cents, right? So you
you're in a position where and I tell
everyone this ask yourself a very simple
question. Do you think troll will ever
pull off just a 2 x? And if the answer
is yes, you can sell half on a double
and now you have a free position that
can do you a 50 x to 100 x on the other
half as well. So that's the thing.
You know, you don't have to actually
wait and hold hoddle to 100 x. You can
once again sell half on a double. So you
don't have to you don't you don't need a
100 x happen, but you're open and
exposed to it to happen, right? And with
memes in my opinion, people want to
expose themselves to like 50 to 100
coins instead of just pick the three to
five best.
You know, get your initial investment
out whenever you're on a double, triple,
quadruple, and you will play way better,
you'll make way more money, you'll make
way less trades, you'll have more time
for other things. You're you know, yeah,
it's just the way to do it in my
opinion. And I'm here once again. When
the market's [__] when when prices are
down, this is when I'm here to tell
people like 10 times extra. Because
look, I'm not hyping anything really.
I'm not I'm not going crazy or anything.
I just want people to think for
themselves. Because if you learn how to
do this right now when the prices are
down, when when there's no attention on
crypto, that's that's the only way you
make 100x. You will never make 100x bro
once the hype is already here. So enjoy
when the hype is not here. And
anticipate, will hype ever come back to
crypto?
If you think no, there will never be
hype again in crypto, then don't put
your money anywhere around this stuff.
But it's like that's such a bad take,
that's such a bad, you know, side to be
on. It's obvious hype will always return
to the space. So then it's just a matter
of determining where does the hype flow
into the most? And it's very obvious.
>> Yep. And guys, let us know in the
comments too, like who that boy? Great
profile picture, good name. It says big
three, Wojak, Uchiya, Troll,
[clears throat]
Gucci Beard says that's all you need to
know.
Uh and people were saying that look,
Uchiya, Yaz says Uchiya. Oh, me and
Ronnie clicked at the same time. Yaz.
Smoking a little doobie
up there with a nice watch on his wrist.
Uchiya is the best play. We have Troll,
Asteroid Uchiya. Now Ronnie
was talking about Troll. We have Troll
Coded, Discuss Wojak, also says X.
>> say one point, which is that uh
people have the What's the hardest thing
people have a time with in crypto? Is
just simply being able to hold when that
thing that they're in isn't getting
market validation or social validation
from others. So it's like
the price can just be there, sitting,
doing nothing.
And And once again, you're not
interested because it's not moving. Once
it starts moving, then you're
interested. Then you see the vision, you
know? You have to learn how to separate
from those two groups of people. You got
to be able to be confident even when the
price is quiet, even when it's not
moving. Once again, that's like the
number one skill that takes you from a
white belt to probably straight to
purple belt in crypto. If you just learn
that one little thing. Once again,
trying to be an example and show that
right now when the prices are down on
everything, you know?
>> I I agree.
>> Crash, I got a question for you. You
know, you talk about holding culture and
those sorts of things. I mean, it's no
surprise it's no like a secret, excuse
me, that we had a lot of people coming
into the crypto space this cycle, you
know, that like meme coins. Phantom
wallet, Solana was their first bit of
exposure. I can't blame those guys who
got absolutely [__] on literally
everything. These president tokens,
these celebrity tokens, everything on
pump fun really. Remember the whole time
on pump fun 60 seconds.
>> What do you tell those guys who don't
know what we had before that are just
new to the space? Like where can they
find alpha? What
>> There's there's different There's
different types of memes, you know? I'm
not going to take the holding culture
onto pump fun [__] And I'm not going
to take the pump fun [__] mentality
and execution over to a Mount Rushmore
meme. So you just got to know what are
you playing, you know? You drive these
different cars differently. You swing a
different club differently.
You know, you you lift weights and what?
Some people suck at it, some people are
good at it.
You got to just be the guy who actually
dedicates yourself
and not not be the guy that sucks at it.
>> [laughter]
>> That sounds so dumb. Like just be good
at it and don't suck at it. But I guess
to me, that's what it feels like. I just
don't think this is hard and I know
people say, "Well, well, you don't think
it's hard, but other people do think
it's hard." Well, if you're listening
and you're listening, okay, plant a seed
on ton. All right, I'm not telling you
what coin to buy. Go plant a seed there.
Find two memes, the best ones you like
the most on the chain. Plan a seed
there. Find two memes on Solana. Plant
your seeds there. Find two, one meme,
three memes on ETH. Plant your seed
there. All right, now you have exposure
to three different chains. So, now if
let's say right I I think Ton is going
to be the
the the the L1 that goes up the most.
But okay, let's say you were wrong in
two instances. Let's say Ton sucked,
Solana sucked, but Ethereum pops the
[__] off again. Which once again, I
don't think Ethereum's going to be the
the the crazy outperformer that does
better than Ton, right? The actual gas,
right? The ETH or the Ton for gas. But
yeah, then you're not dependent on one
outcome. You're not dependent on one
thing, you know?
The more people try to sell one thing to
go into the other,
eventually just leads to regret. Um and
whenever you don't really keep track of
what are you doing, it leads to a lot of
impulsive trades. Like, okay, so I was
in this trade. I was up 10 grand. And
then I quickly rotated to this thing.
Oh, now I lost three grand. And then I
quickly rotated to that and I won lost
three grand. And before you know it, you
have like 100 different trades that you
can't really track. What did you do with
your life? Like you probably don't
remember a lot of these trades you took
or they kind of just happened and they
were impulsive. I think impulsiveness is
one of the greatest things you should
you have to learn to avoid in crypto cuz
impulsiveness gets you killed. You just
want you want to save your money for the
best times and the things you're most
confident in. If you If you can do that,
if you can avoid 99% of [__] you will
do instantly 100 times better. But most
people can't avoid 99% of [__] Most
people can't go three days without
chasing the next dopamine hit. And so
they end up getting involved with [__]
that they're going to regret. And that's
the thing, bro. If you learn this,
you're going to do so much better. But
once again, it's so much easier to wake
up the next day without a plan or you're
not really even thinking. You just see
some coin and you're like, "Bam, rotate
into that. Bam, rotate into that."
Before you know it, you lost your money
and you sit there thinking like, damn,
if I would have just kept my 10 grand
here, how much that would that be? You
look back two years later, it's worth
280 grand if you held, you know?
>> That makes you hate meme coins, right?
That makes you like
>> And you hate meme coins. You hate meme
coins.
>> Yeah, and you also
>> Yeah, also learn how to rotate
into things low when someone's saying
something, cuz I'm not I'm not going to
sit here and lie to you. If a meme on
Ton is hitting 5 billion market cap,
that's not the time to make
life-changing gains anymore. You know,
yes, it could go from 5 billion to 10
billion. Could even go from 5 billion to
15 billion. But, that's not the time
where you go and put 100 grand in. Then,
the time to put 100 grand in is
in the [__] depression, right? This
is the meme coin depression. So, 100
grand in oot
100 grand in a troll, 100 grand, you
know, into some Ton meme, 100 grand into
some ETH meme. And just sit on it. And
and and keep keep your bets limited.
Keep Keep your bets limited, and and
don't freaking uh over rotate, over
play, man. That's how you get killed.
>> Yeah. Little 40 in slip there, but yeah,
man. No, I agree.
>> It's Well, it's easier It's easier said
than done, you know, at the end of the
day, because
like No, we live in a dopamine society,
bro. It's like, well, if I like and
honestly, bro, like sometimes
I feel more, let's say I put 15,000 on a
hockey game. I actually feel more when I
lose that money versus when I win 5K, so
Like, dude, people are dope me addicts.
They're just looking for something. What
are they supposed to do? Crash with
their own [__] pump fund, taking a
bunch of Adderall at 3:00 a.m., [__]
getting rugged? Like, just buy a meme
coin and hold it for 3 years and then
sell it? Like, what should we do with
our time? Like, people need something to
do. I mean, what do you do? You You've
invested into meme coins right now.
You're holding long-term. You're not
touching them. Are you buying more when
it dips? Are you kind of just like
sitting from the side? Like, for Troll,
for example, you obviously bought Troll.
You're like bull posting it very hard. I
haven't seen you bull post like that in
years.
Um, but is that what you're doing or
just kind of bull like you're not you're
not constantly on pump fun and live new
pairs buying stuff? Like what do you do
personally to get that dopamine mix?
Does it come outside of crypto? Are you
doing jujitsu or are you hanging out
with friends? Like what are you doing?
>> I like to have different baskets in your
life, you know? So, all right, means
it's just one of 10 baskets, you know? I
have my places that I'm renovating,
decorating. I love that [__] you know?
I love decorating, having nice lighting,
having nice sofas, having all the nice
stuff, making everything perfect, you
know? I love that stuff. So, okay,
that's another basket in my life. Making
sure my family's good with money, that's
another basket in my life. Training,
right? So, I go to Muay Thai, that's
another basket in my life. And look,
Muay Thai, dude, I for me it it it's
painful. I for me I find jujitsu to be
way easier on my body.
>> Way easier?
>> Yeah,
yeah, yeah, yeah. And
yeah, for some reason striking is a lot
harder for me than than rolling. So,
anyways, I dude, I can't tell you how
many days I go and I'm just like, man,
[__] I don't want to do this. It hurts,
you know? And it doesn't matter. You
just go and do it. That's one basket of
your life. You only need to suffer one
to two hours that day. Get it done. And
you know, I I was training six days a
week. Now I'm only training around three
days a week. Uh, you know, so I can be
here more on the computer and focus a
little more.
But yeah, and and then, you know,
there's other baskets, too. One of my
baskets is even gambling, right?
Another basket. You can have a few cars.
Another basket, bro, you can have some
collectibles like Pokémon cards. So, you
have all these different baskets going
on for you in life. Whenever you fail in
one basket or something's not going
great in one or two baskets, you have
another basket that's giving you hope,
that's giving you, you know, that you're
progressing in. So, hey, if the market's
down, once again, I know that through my
suffering I'm growing somewhere else. Or
through my enjoyment I'm making my
places neater, making my places nicer,
or I'm, you know, you can always be
improving in some other baskets. So, if
you're actually improving and have other
[__] going for you, you don't have to
sit there and gamble on new launches and
stuff all the time because you already
know, okay, let me reduce this down to
the simplest form and make this the
easiest way that I can make money, you
know, while freeing up time for myself.
And I think the most efficient way to do
that is pick three of the five three to
the five best memes that you truly
believe out there. Figure it out for
yourself, you know, I'm not I'm not
shilling
you know, a lot of stuff because I know
that a lot of these memes there's so
much bigger than me and they shouldn't
be about me. And I feel sometimes people
try to reduce a meme to being about me
like oh did crash call it or oh crash
call oh okay oh no, it's not about that,
bro. It's not about anyone calling it.
What a lot of people don't realize and
it, you know, I I I understand why they
think that. I was talking about this in
a chat. It's not the person who calls
anything.
It's just about the call. Like it's
about if the call is right. Like I
promise you if I go to do five bad calls
tomorrow, it doesn't matter.
My word means nothing. So, it's not once
again, it's not about the call. It's not
about the person. It's about just being
correct in the thing. Like are you
correct about the, you know, that future
outcome? If you are, that's the only
thing that matters. And yes, I'm a
person that maybe some people listen to.
So, I amplify maybe slightly the results
of things, but I don't I'm not one to
actually push it. I'm actually just
correct in advance and I'm trying to
even show people even more this time
around than ever before that being
correct is the most important thing. If
you be correct, everything follows. You
be correct, that matters far more than
becoming some influencer. It matters far
more than having followers. It matters
far more than anything else. Be correct.
Do the right things. Focus on the right
baskets. Everything takes care of
itself, you know.
>> Absolutely. 100% agree. I got two more
things for you, Crasher, and then we'll
let you go. I know your time is very,
very valuable, but uh
I've been partnered with RainBet, I
think the number one online crypto
casino in the entire world. Uh they're
great sponsor of the Jake and Show. We
appreciate them. I saw recently you
officially announced your partnership
with RainBet. Tell us a little bit about
what that is about.
>> Well, it's a 3-month little agreement we
have. Basically, they gave me 500 grand.
If I double it, I get to
I get to give away 250,000.
So,
that's uh yeah, it's a little thing.
Bro, I uh lately, this last month, I've
been on the best betting run uh for me.
It was 9 grand into 200 grand.
>> Whoa, damn.
>> Why 9 grand? It's cuz I pulled out 10
grand to go bet, but then I gave 1 grand
to my family member who wanted to bet.
So, that's why I specifically 9 grand to
200 grand the last month. For me, that's
my best run is like a 20x
>> What are you cooking?
UFC?
>> I've been doing UFC, basketball, MLB,
and then my family member who also bets,
he is my Valorant quant. So, he knows
like the video games. So, I I kind of
watch some of the video games.
Valorant and CS:GO, but I'm not like
actually good at those myself or truly
knowledgeable about those. But, I just
tell my family member and it's a fun way
for us to spend time with like just
bet together.
>> UFC alpha for you. The guy to my left or
my right, I don't know. This guy over
here. Hey, I try. He's [__] good at
UFC. He literally owned me. Bro, Sean
Strickland versus Khamzat, he calls me.
He goes, "Sean Strickland is going to
beat him." He told me exactly how and
that happened. I was like, "Sean
Strickland was what? Plus
400? 800? I don't even know what it
was."
>> Bet odds.
>> Plus 400 and he ended up winning.
>> Yeah.
I mean, some of these are easy, though.
You got to Like, that's not easy. I'm a
UFC We're you We're MMA guy. I'm balls
deep in that [__]
>> So I'm Crasher. Crasher, if you want to
turn this $500,000 into a million
dollars with RainBet and you need picks
from UFC, I would say call Rodney cuz
he's I mean he's like 70-80% which is
pretty unreal.
>> No, I mean we both
>> over Justin Gaethje, no one did. I
picked a lot of main events and no one
did.
>> I picked Paddy.
>> Yeah, I picked I picked Gaethje as well.
>> I picked Paddy in that fight. Yeah, I
mean
>> UFC is tough though.
>> People always ask me in chats, right?
Oh, who who you got this weekend? Who
you got? I always tell them in chats,
what's the difference? I'm I'm betting
on this [__] myself. People ask me every
weekend, every week, you know. The only
difference now, dude, I get, you know,
and and I whenever I bet, I always
whenever I make money, I I give away
some of my profit as well. It's what I
do naturally cuz I have a little, I
don't know if it's a philosophy or what.
Uh but basically, look, if you make
$10,000 and you share $1,000, right? You
give $500 to two guys,
you just created a positive that can't
be taken from the earth, right? Like
like okay, you made 10 grand. That's one
positive.
Now you just multiplied it. You turned
it into two more positives for other
people. Now, those guys, it's risk-free
for them. They just got $500 spawned
into their lap. So, if even if they lose
500, it couldn't have possibly been a
negative for their life. Whereas you, if
you make 10 grand and you blow the 10
grand, you went from positive back to
neutral.
Or you can even go back to negative. But
if when you're up, you simply multiply
that and turn it into more positives on
earth, those those positives can't be
erased from earth. They can never turn
into negatives. Yeah. So,
that's just how I do it and it makes
makes things fun for me. I like to win
and share my money and that's it.
>> Yeah, I'll tell you what. I think really
I've never met Crash, guys. We've only
talked online like this, but we would
actually be probably best friends,
Rodney. I know you're my best friend
now, but Crash would probably replace
you as number one cuz we just don't
>> That's the same [__]
>> How gay is that to say that, right?
>> [laughter]
>> What do you what do you mean?
>> the truth, bro. We both pass out when we
get our blood drawn. Although I used to
pass out. I The more IVs you get, bro,
Rodney's a sicko. You can get IVs here.
He [__] watches the needle go in. He
likes it. He's a sicko, but Crash, real
quick, on that RainBet, so shout out to
RainBet. They sponsor both of us now,
but I turned $20,000.
So, first off, I I I was doing NHL bets
on a cooker. I lost three straight.
Like, my team I was betting on lost in
overtime. I'm like depressed. I'm like,
I just lost 40K. I'm like, [__] or 30K,
whatever it was. Called my buddy. I'm
I'm like, I'm done. And then after I go
in the sauna, I'm like, you know what?
I'm going to put 20,000 more. If I lose
it, I'm done forever. If I win, I'm
going to keep it running. I go eight for
my next nine. Technically, eight for
eight and I lost the last one. Turned
20K into like 75K. Cashed it out of
RainBet. Thanks, RainBet. And I put the
down payment for a boat. So,
that's a that was a good thing. And then
uh yeah. So,
>> It's taking your money.
>> Get RainBet.
>> Gambling's tough though, man. You get
like Crash, you're hot right now. In the
same way you're hot, like dude, I've
been so [__] hot and then I've lost
my last like six NHL bets. I'm just
like, [__] But guess what? There's a
good quote on gambling. I'll leave you
with this and we'll
>> talk about one more thing. A good quote
quote on gambling, you don't ever lose
in gambling. You either run out of money
or you eventually win. And that's our
goal to eventually win.
Now, last time
>> Can I can I say that I think just the
most important thing is
dude, uh I I really believe at worse,
it's a rich man's Netflix subscription.
Now, I would try to avoid
being, you know, the the where I hate
gambling is if you're someone let's say
you only have $500 and instead of trying
to go do something with your life, you
just want to gamble. I don't think
that's cool. You know, I've seen it with
my own family member uh who he's a
little younger than me, right? And he
instead of go start like a business or
do something with his life, he'll
gamble. And we know that. He's he's my
family, right? I'm not going to go into
our relation He's my family. And you
know, we always talk about it and stuff.
And but I know that we both wouldn't
have it any other way for him. Like it's
part of his life. That's what he does
and we have he has no regret, you know,
he gets a lot of experience and
knowledge doing it and he's self-aware
about it and anyways, it's like
I think the best thing to do you lock
in, you make a lot of money and enjoy as
Netflix subscription. The truth is dude,
if you have different baskets of your
[clears throat] life. Like once again,
gambling is like 1/10, 1/11, 1/12, one
you know, one basket of many. So, you
know, let's say I lose 20 grand on a
bet, okay, I probably just made 30 grand
on this ton long I had open. This 33
grand I made on a near long. I have my
memes that go up. I have my real estate,
you know, so once you once you kind of
are a little diversified out and you
already have a bunch of [__] going for
you dude, it's okay to once again,
either way your your investment
portfolio is going to be down at some
point. I you you know, you're going to
be down somewhere. So as long as you're
improving in other baskets, it doesn't
you're always going to have something
going for you. And while you might
actually your investment portfolio might
be going down, you might be going on a
phenomenal gambling run like 9k to 200k
which keeps your spirits up while your
portfolio is going down. It's like
the only people I've ever seen complain
about this [__] bro are people that are
unsuccessful or like gay bro. Like
there's no I I don't I don't really see
like any successful people be like Oh,
dur dur dur. I'll never
>> Look, I look no one loves the gays more
than Jake and love the gay loves the
gays but the gays do hate gambling. It's
like there's something in San Francisco
in the tap water. They hate gambling.
But the thing about gambling though like
I said so I turned 20k into 70
and like recently I just lost 20k in a
Colorado Avalanche bet which Las Vegas
Knights Golden Knights should not be
Colorado at home. What the [__] But
it's like you're kind of playing with
house money and if you're not playing
with house money you're just losing
losing losing losing then you [__]
suck at gambling and you need to stop
doing it. But if you're cooking, like
Crash is cooking right now, I was
cooking on NHL, it's like you're Yes, it
sucks to lose 20k, but that 20k is money
that you made from winning, right? So,
that's kind of how I look at it. Like,
you're not going to win them all. You're
not going to make every single coin
prediction right.
>> cuz look, so nine nine grand, right?
That's what I start with.
>> It's crazy.
>> Uh I turn that to 80 to 100k. I say 80
to 100 because some of it was an active
futures, like the Knicks to make it to
the finals, San Antonio Spurs to beat
the Knicks in the finals. Like, so I had
some future bets that once again,
they're just chilling there. So,
>> work, too.
>> You could cash them out, right? Or you
could leave them running. So, that's why
I say 80 to 100 grand cuz 80 grand is
about what I had. So, I withdraw 53
grand, and I keep around 20-ish K
running on the you know, whatever future
bet I'm going to place, plus I have the
futures bets. So, anyways, then from
there,
I get aggressive with whatever 10 grand
or 10 grand uh
10 grand or 20 grand I leave in the
account. So, now instead of like playing
safer, right? Cuz I already withdrew 53
grand. Now I got once again, 20-ish
grand running. So, you can size up and
instead of, you know, risking like like
whenever I start with nine grand, I'll
only put like maybe two grand on a bet,
three grand on a bet, you know? Uh if
I'm trying to play smart.
But then at the end of it, right? Now
that you've sized up, you've already
withdrew your profit, now you can size
up on those uh remaining amount knowing
you can just pull another 10 grand out
and start your next run, right? So,
>> [clears throat]
>> that's what I do. Now, I withdrew over
130 grand. I have 70 grand in the
account right now. And so, guess what?
If I, you know, blow this
whatever is there, I still have 130
grand. Guess what? I can always start a
future on with just 10 grand, and now I
can go for it again, you know? So,
>> I I Bro, it's the same
It's the same thing with the meme coin,
bro. You can be up 100x and round trip
it fully, or you can sell half on a
double, sell a third on a triple.
You know, it's all about how you play
and how you what's your perspective, you
know? You can play things however you
want.
>> Absolutely. Shout out to my guy Dom
Woods. It's not gambling if you're
winning. Jimmy says, "What is the best
crypto casino? I like Rainbet. I love
Rainbet. I don't like Rainbet." Crypt,
you can deposit any crypto, instant
withdrawals, and they pay you right
away. My guy KP says top supercycle
crash. Do me a favor, give a shout out
to Twisty Sense.
Kyle, he actually works with us and he's
a big fan of crash. He actually showed
me a screenshot. He He watched your
first YouTube video on Brett the day it
went live, like the first one. He some
He went to the Brett page, screenshotted
it. 200 followers on the base Brett
page. That's Twisty Sense. He's been
following you for years. Give him a
shout out if [clears throat] you can.
>> What's up, Twisty? Beast, bro. Thank
you, bro. I don't say it enough. I don't
say thank you enough to the people that
are cool cuz seems like sometimes we
focus more on the people that are
annoying. So, just thanks, Twisty, and
everyone, bro. Like everyone that's so
kind, you know? Um because, yeah, man,
sometimes when I
you know, I feel like lately I've been
way more like better at uh
you know, seeing comments and like it
doesn't bother me at all anymore. But,
before, yeah, it took more time, you
know, to like develop that. But, dude,
sometimes before in the past I'm just
like, "Man, these [__] people are so
annoying. Why am I I I I should just
pack up." I just like, "Why am I on here
anymore? I don't need to be here. I got
plenty of money to not have to be here,
you know?" And I've bro, I've even
thought about you know, maybe I
shouldn't even say this, but bro, I've
I've thought about like, "Man, what if I
just sell my account? Just say [__] it,
man. Just [__] leave this." You know,
I'll take the extra bag, sell the
account, and just be done with this.
But, you know, sometimes though it
really is worth it. Sometimes it's worth
it to be here.
>> it, bro. I'm not going to let you do
that.
I'm not going to let you do that. I
don't know where you live, but I'll come
find you and I'll come talk some sense
into you.
>> You know, I was thinking the the if I
sold a
my account, I would go start a smaller
account
>> [laughter]
>> I like I like being a small account
because when you're smaller, more people
are supportive and cool and it's like a
tighter circle. Whereas once your
account kind of gets bigger and hits the
algorithm, starts attracting a lot of
casuals and like people that don't
actually know you or didn't follow you
before, so they're just very casual
viewers that, you know, they're they're
very frail frail viewers or like
followers, you know? So I like being a
small account.
And yeah, I mean it's part of the game,
but it's not [clears throat] a game that
I have to play, right? I can just
go to I can just go become a small
account and actually enjoy the game
again or do things like, you know, more
more supportive cast around you. I was
reading this like
what is it? Notes from not Marcus
Aurelius, it was someone else
Seneca.
>> Meditations greatest book ever. Seneca?
Yeah, he's great too.
>> Yeah, so
>> Rodney be best friends.
Rodney doesn't need to Marcus Aurelius.
We're not even best friends.
>> [laughter]
>> And he was talking about like in in in
in the book like, "Hey,
once you get past a certain point where
the people around you are not supportive
anymore and you know, when you try to
tell people it doesn't it doesn't really
you're preaching to the wrong people
once you get past a certain point. He's
like, "Well, that's the point where I
start writing my book for the future
generations. That's where I stop wasting
my time giving these speeches or these
times with people locally anymore
because I've gotten too big that they
don't care anymore basically. So yeah,
it's just kind of like that. It's like
if you're surrounded by people that are
just talking [__] and that don't see the
value in what you're doing, you might as
well just
back it up maybe. Of course, you know,
then dude, I look up to people like even
like Jake Paul, bro. Jake Paul is so big
and he has got so many people that [__]
on him, but dude, look at him. He got
his jaw like broken [__] in his last
fight and I love bro, I respect the [__]
out of him.
Even though you know, I'll watch
interviews of Jake Paul and I'll be
like, he's so cringe right now. Like,
this is so dumb. And then, guess what? I
still respect the [__] out of him
because at the end of the day, bro,
other people can sit on the couch and
criticize all they want. He's actually
doing it. And yeah, I don't know.
There's spectators, there's doers. And
yeah, I don't know.
>> Absolutely. 6.8 thousand people are here
on X right now. I have one more topic I
want to talk to you about, but I think
before we get to that, I just want to
say that, bro, you just cannot read
comments and let other people influence
you. You know, that's one thing that
Marcus Aurelius says, right? I I like I
read his book through and through and he
talks about the fact that these people
who are throwing stones at you, that are
criticizing you, who are they? Do you
even respect them? Like that guy that's
on there right now saying, "Crash is a
scammer." He's probably in his bed, fat
as [__] eating pizza, beating off six
times a day with [__] lotion and
trash all over his room. You care, but
you see it written. And then someone
like Kyle and Henok who's saying, "Let's
go, the goat." Right? Who are supporting
you, you take that in, right? But you
you focus, not you in specific, but
humans, right? We have this negativity
bias. You focus on that one negative
comment. There could be 99 people in
here that say, "Crash, you're great.
You're Brett call. Oh my god, I love
you." But one guy's going to be like,
"Crash is a scammer." And your brain
will focus on that. It won't think about
what Kyle said when he's at my house
saying, "Bro, I love Crash. I've been
following for 3 years. Look at this Look
at this screenshot of Brett from his
call. I made money on Brett." Like,
that's cool. But then that one guy's
like, "Dude, you [__] up." And like
that's what our brains focus on. So,
it's like you just got to value. Maybe
if like someone you respect like Jake
Paul is saying, "Hey, Crash, you're
doing this wrong or that wrong." You'd
be like, "Yeah, maybe I am doing
something wrong." But people that you
don't care about, people that you don't
even You wouldn't even give them the
time of day if you saw them because
they're that worthless, why would you
value their opinion at all?
>> There's a couple people that um
hearing their like little quotes kind of
help. And it'll be like, "Okay, so that
comment, look at Do you think it's true?
If it's true,
then it's your fault. You know, like
then okay, then they're right. Why can
you Why could you be mad at them for
saying that, you know? But, if you look
at the comment and just say, okay, is it
true?
And it's like, name me
>> hey, look at that [__] Look at
Hey, look at He's taking time out of his
day to watch this stream and he's
>> There's no way you got more money than
all three of us combined, but you can't
fix that [__] hair on the top.
>> He's also trolling that, bro. He's
probably trolling.
>> Oh, for sure, yeah.
>> Boy.
Speaking of troll.
>> Uh last thing cuz I do have to go out uh
by 6:30. I got a hot date. Hot date
crash. We have 7,000 people on here
right now. We did an impromptu stream
back in October. [clears throat]
Impromptu stream back in October. We
have like 60 or 70,000 people on. It was
when Astor, the decentralized exchange
that's backed by BNB chain by CZ Binance
by Easy Labs went live. The Astor chart,
I mean, it went parabolic, crash. You
called it first, like at 32 cents, I
think it was. It went all the way up to
$2.50.
This was Think about it. This was like
peak bull run, right? October. Uh the
price has now kind of subsided. I mean,
there was a lot of [__] that happened in
crypto space, the massive liquidation
events. I mean, Astor was hit pretty
hard by that. Uh went all the way down
to 50 cents, which I had limit orders
set, massive limit orders set in Astor
DEX that I didn't even know about, like
$50,000 they placed. I'm so happy they
did. Astor's sitting at 67 cents. I have
personally never sold a single token.
Still bullish. You were just talking
about futures on Ton. Uh perpetual
decentralized exchanges are big,
leverage trading's big. What's your
thought on Astor moving into this next
cycle?
>> Yeah, so
I uh a lot of people going to hate this,
but So, I was up I put $1 million in
Astor. I was up $4 million at the peak.
And what I always do, bro, when I'm up
like millions on something, I always go
and I look to negotiate a deal. I don't
care if it's like a little car or a
little something, whatever. Uh in this
case, I was trying to negotiate this
ocean front penthouse for my family so
that they could live close by to me.
And there was some [__] about how
the owner, you know, they put they had
it listed for sale and then they end up
not wanting to sell because their kid
had some problem in school or some
[__] So anyways, bro, I'm there
like pressing on the deal like, "Hey,
come on, come on, let's do it, let's do
it, let's do it." Cuz that's like the
best time, bro, is when you're up 4
million, bro. Bam, you can convert 1.2
million and you have a new place that
you're never you're not going to regret
it. And you can always sell it later if
you want, but it feels great to like
convert that moment. That never gets
accepted because of that school excuse
of this kid of these people, whatever,
[__] I'm pissed. So start round
tripping. Ultimately, instead of getting
my initials out at the peak like when
I'm trying to negotiate this deal, I end
up getting my initials out at a $1
ASTOR, which is about two and a half
times higher than where I entered. And
so I do feel like the trade at that
point was way stronger than it is
currently, but I still think that ASTOR
is going to have a a pump up later. The
thing is that even if it pumps up later,
right? The thing about ASTOR, the
biggest and best part about it for me
was
you had this very easy narrative or
logical case to be like, "Okay, ASTOR
should be half of hype." Right? Half of
hyperliquid.
But now a lot of the haters and a lot of
people they were right about ASTOR where
it's like I feel like it hasn't really
developed that much of people using it
like it could have by now, you know?
Now, I'm not saying that they don't have
tricks up their sleeve to get a lot of
people incentivized to use ASTOR and
that's still very doable. But I'm just
saying the the case was a lot stronger
then and there to reach half of the
market cap of hype and now that it's
kind of lost that momentum and case to
definitively be half of hype or even
flip hype, I feel that that loses a lot
of the power of the trade. Now that hype
has with more time just shown that hey,
it's still number one no matter what. So
once again, I do think it makes it takes
out a lot of the firepower of the trade.
And that's why bro, you always got to
take your initials out when you're up
because yeah, things can develop way
better.
And also things can slow down and not go
as good as maybe you you plan for. So
initials out, everything good. Of
course, I'm really salty that I didn't
get that purchase in basically at the
top bro. That's why I always negotiate
deals when things are running like that.
And that sucks. But yeah,
uh I think Astra's still going to do you
know, do a run. But here's the thing,
can I justify
Astra significantly more than I could
some other plays out there in the
market? And that's the that's once again
where is a trade can lose some of its
fire power is because it's like okay,
well, in relation to some other things,
do people want to hold it? And yeah, I
think some people will hold Astra right
now thinking like okay, it's an easy two
to three X. But a lot of people will
also look at plenty of other things and
say well, this is an easy five X or 10
X. So just that's once again, sucks out
a lot of the the power of the trade. And
so I do think it's a weaker trade than
it was before. I still think yeah, it
can easily do a two to three X here. But
once again, just don't think it's going
to be as strong of a trade as I
initially was hoping for it to be.
>> Mhm, got you. And everybody's open to
their own opinions. I still believe it's
going to be a $10 plus token just
because of who is backing it. I mean,
the the BNB ecosystem, the BNB and
chain, they're one of the most
successful organizations in crypto. They
have the most money. We saw it with the
BNB meme coin super cycle happen. I mean
like just out of thin air, every coin
going to 500 million. Like there's so
much money in the BNB ecosystem. CZ
Binance has put his name on it. And
we've seen when people come after CZ
Binance, he literally throws them in
jail and Drake starts rapping about them
uh
in prison. But I think that Astra will
trade above $10. I'm highly convicted.
People think I'm I'm paid by them. I'm
not paid. Bought them, saw my money go
up, never sold a dollar, put more money
in, and I'm betting on CZ Binance,
betting on the BNB chain, and everything
I did.
>> Like, you haven't said how much you put
in. I'm very upfront. I put a million
into it, I was up 4 million. And people
want to call that paid shill. No [__]
I'm going to be excited about a position
I'm up 4 million on, you know?
>> Exactly.
>> It's It's not paid shill, [__]
It's called, bro, we finally had a big
play, first one in a while in the
market. You know, my gosh. You
If I'm
>> paid to shill, I put paid promotion.
Like Like right every RainBet post, they
It's a partnership, right? Like when I'm
talking about Useless I bought in. I'm
talking like I There's no problem with I
have a big We all have big platforms. I
have 400,000 followers in here. If
someone wants to pay me to talk about
it, I'll say paid promotion. But if I
buy something and bull post it, I'm
buying and bull posting it. There's no
problem I have no problem saying that I
I'm I'm paid by something. But Astro I'm
not paid by, I just really believe in CZ
Binance um in the power of him. And if
he start Dude, he put $2 million in at a
dollar. If he starts bull posting again
with the money comes back in, obviously
perpetual exchanges are going to be big.
Binance is the number one exchange. It
makes sense they're going to have a a
really good decentralized exchange. And
the higher that hype goes, I think it's
going to be more bullish for Astro in
the long run. But boys, as I mentioned,
I got to be somewhere in 30 minutes. We
might have to wrap this up. But Crash,
if we want to do it again at some point,
anytime, you are welcome on here. And
please don't ever quit because you are a
net net net net net triple net quadruple
net positive for the crypto space. I
think this stream's going to go down in
history. I'm going to clip up some stuff
about what we talked about with Troll
and post it later. We're going to come
back in 2 years and see if Troll is in
the Mount Rushmore of meme coins. I do
own Troll.
>> is, bro. The price just hasn't caught up
to that reality. That's That's what you
got to know, you know? This stuff is
easy. It just It just doesn't mean that
the price catches on right away, you
know?
>> Hey, give us some
>> Absolutely.
>> Guys, uh let me see some love for Crash
in in comments. Yoda,
>> Everybody loves
>> Yes,
guys, show some love to Crash cuz he's
obviously seeing too much negative
comments. All I see is positive comments
when I go for Crash.
>> No, there's a lot of positive, man. I
just, once again, there could be two
negative comments out of 10. Always look
at the two negative. But dude, what out
of 100?
Truly, bro, I it doesn't it does not
bother me even 5% as much as it used to,
man, so I truly am getting better at
just looking at it.
>> I don't even read it, bro. I don't even
read it. I mean, if you self-audit and
you [__] look in the mirror and say,
"Hey, am I putting my best foot
forward?" And look, it's the crypto
space. Sometimes you talk about
something that goes up, sometimes you
talk about something that goes down. If
you're watching this, you say like,
"What what the [__] Jake?" It's like,
"Dude, let me see your portfolio." I
guarantee you invest in [__] that goes
up, and I guarantee you invest in [__]
that goes down. It's part of being a
coin. As long as you put your best foot
forward, you know, you try to do good,
you know, you try to do good by others,
yourself, tokens, then there's nothing
wrong, right? If you're paid to do
something, you say you're paid. If you
buy something, you say you buy. Like,
you're never going to be perfect. And
honestly, like I said, like the market
is really is, don't [__] listen to
the fat ass who's 45 years old living in
his grandmother's basement that's
calling you a scammer cuz if you saw him
on the street with his [__] Led
Zeppelin fat beer belly,
>> I would have fought him anyway.
>> [__] Led Zeppelin, Rodney. Catching
strays.
He caught a stray. It's Iceman, dog. And
that's it, guys. I got to run. 6:30,
Crash, I love you. You're not my new
best friend. Rodney, I love you. You're
still my best friend. I'm joking. And uh
everybody that tuned in, we [__] love
you. We talked about Troll, I talked
about Udyr, we talked about Jesse
Pollak,
>> and Diamond Troll.
>> Me and Rodney are back every single
Monday, Wednesday, Friday. We'll be back
on Monday
at 4:00 p.m. Eastern Standard Time. Have
a good weekend. We'll see you guys soon.